<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/2/2016 4:34:53 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TRADING_POST_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built over a Road that connects two Cities, doubled if built over a Railroad instead. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if a Trade Route passes over this Village, doubled in post-Industrial era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_LUMBERMILL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 Lumber Mills adjacent to this Lumber Mill.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TERRACE_FARM_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every Terrace Farm or Mountains adjacent to this Terrace Farm. Adds +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to nearby Farms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to nearby Villages and Towns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_WATER_HELP">
			<Text>Allows land units to traverse this Coast tile. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to nearby Villages and Towns. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONGOLIA_ORDO">
			<Text>Ordo</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONGOLIA_ORDO_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONGOLIA_ORDO_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Simply translated, “ordo” means “palace tent.” However, an ordo was something much more than just a simple tent —- it was the center of the tribe for the nomadic Mongolians.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An ordo served as the headquarters and main encampment for the Khan and his warriors. Though built for travel, it had style, from simple decorations to carefully sewn patterns. The ordo moved with the Khan and his warriors as they went on campaign, ensuring they always felt at home no matter where they traveled.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You can construct an Ordo anywhere within your territory, or directly adjacent to your territory. Upon constructing the Ordo, your Military Unit Supply Cap will increase by 1, and your Culture borders will also expand to surround the Ordo on all sides by one hex. If the new Culture border claims hexes already owned by another civilization, you will incur a diplomatic penalty as a result. Unlike the Citadel, any enemy unit which ends its turn next to an Ordo takes no damage.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONGOLIA_ORDO_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian Great Person Tile Improvement, replacing the Citadel. Provides [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building an Ordo claims adjacent tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Units standing on an Ordo receive +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense and +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement for that turn. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONGOLIA_ORDO">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_MONGOLIA_ORDO]Ordo[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONGOLIA_ORDO_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built in owned territory or adjacent to your own borders in an unowned tile, and cannot be adjacent to other Ordos. Constructing the Ordo will expand your Culture borders to surround the Ordo, increase your [ICON_WAR] Military Unit Supply Cap by 1, and will consume this unit. If the new Culture border claims hexes already owned by another civilization, you will incur a diplomatic penalty as a result. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength and +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement for any Unit stationed in this tile. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONGOLIA_ORDO_REC">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE]Unique Mongolian Tile Improvement. Provides [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Gives a [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus and [ICON_MOVES] Movement to units stationed on it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EKI">
			<Text>Eki</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_EKI_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_EKI_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]'Eki' is a term that the Huns likely used to describe the earth, particularly that which was essential to grazing livestock. Nomadic pastoralism is a form of pastoralism where livestock are herded in order to find fresh pastures on which to graze. Strictly speaking, true nomads follow an irregular pattern of movement, in contrast with transhumance where seasonal pastures are fixed. However this distinction is often not observed and the term nomad used for both—in historical cases the regularity of movements is often unknown in any case. The herded livestock include cattle, yaks, sheep, goats, reindeer, horses, donkeys or camels, or mixtures of species. Nomadic pastoralism is commonly practised in regions with little arable land, typically in the developing world. Of the estimated 30 to 40 million nomadic pastoralists worldwide, most are found in central Asia and the Sahel region of West Africa. Increasing numbers of stock may lead to overgrazing of the area and desertification if lands are not allowed to fully recover between one grazing period and the next. Increased enclosure and fencing of land has reduced the amount of land available for this practice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_EKI_HELP">
			<Text>An Eki can only be built on flat land tiles without access to Fresh Water. It provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_FOOD] Food, as well as additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent to two[ENDCOLOR] other Eki. Removes any features on the tile. Can be built [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in or adjacent to[ENDCOLOR] Hunnic territory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_EKI]Eki[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI_HELP">
		    <Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 Ekis adjacent to this Eki. Must be build on flat tiles without access to Fresh Water. Can be built [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in or adjacent to[ENDCOLOR] Hunnic territory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building in neutral territory may encourage cities to naturally expand to this Eki.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_FOOD] Food. Provides additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent to two[ENDCOLOR] other Eki. Can be built [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in or adjacent to[ENDCOLOR] Hunnic territory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Hacienda</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:a</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_TEXT">
			<Text>Haciendas are colonial estates constructed by the Spanish for the administration and extraction of resources from their native subjects. Haciendas were based on grants of property and enterprise, rather than the strict grant of indigenous labor as described by the older Encomienda system. Haciendas were generally large estates, but the nature of the work varied from plantations, to mining, to factories.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The owner of a Hacienda was called a Hacendado, but the wealthy landowners rarely visited their holdings and preferred to live in nearby cities. Day-to-day operations of a Hacienda were the responsibility of hired managers. Some unusually large and profitable Haciendas were the property of the Roman Catholic Church, exacerbating tension between native laborers and their Christian taskmasters.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Hacienda system was abolished in most countries after the dissolution of the Spanish Empire, but with mixed results. Efforts to break apart the large estates into individual holdings for subsistence farmers led to crushing poverty in some South American nations. In contrast, Latin American and Filipino Haciendas were mostly left intact, but without the same legal standing or permissions of their colonial past.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Gains additional yields for each adjacent Resource:[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Bonus Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Strategic Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Luxury Resources</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built next to another Hacienda. Provides [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Gains additional yields for each adjacent Resource:[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Bonus Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Strategic Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Luxury Resources</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SPAIN_HACIENDA]Hacienda[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>+3 [ICON_Food] Food for each adjacent Bonus Resource, +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for each adjacent Strategic Resource, and +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for each adjacent Luxury Resource.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SPAIN_HACIENDA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE]Gains [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from adjacent resources.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_JFD_MACHU_PICCHU">
			<Text>Mountain City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KUNA">
			<Text>Kuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_KUNA_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_KUNA_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]'Kuna' is the Mayan word for temple or church. Mayan Kuna were similar in design to the ziggurats and pyramids of Eurasia. Though the Kuna themselves are largely all that remain of these ancient sites, they were once the focal points of large cities. Most famous of these is Chichen Itza, a sight so grand that it qualifies as a World Wonder!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_KUNA_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be constructed in Forests or Jungles, and cannot be adjacent to another Kuna. Generates [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_KUNA]Kuna[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built adjacent to another Kuna. Does not remove features on the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE">
			<Text>Encampment</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE_TEXT">
			<Text>An Encampment can only be built on flat tiles, and no two Encampments can be adjacent. It provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Encampments provide a small defense modifier to units stationed on them, and damage nearby enemy units (5) if they end their turn on or next to an Encampment. Can only be built in Shoshone territory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]A tipi is a conical tent, traditionally made of animal skins, and wooden poles. The tipi was used in the encampments of nomadic tribes of the Great Plains in North America. Tipis are stereotypically associated with Native Americans in the United States in general, however Native Americans from places other than the Great Plains mostly used different types of dwellings. The tipi is durable, provides warmth and comfort in winter, is cool in the heat of summer, and is dry during heavy rains. Tipis could be disassembled and packed away quickly when a tribe decided to move and could be reconstructed quickly upon settling in a new area. This portability was important to Plains Indians with their nomadic lifestyle. Modern tipi covers are usually made of canvas. Contemporary users of tipis include historical reenactors, back-to-the-land devotees, and Native American families attending powwows or encampments who wish to preserve and pass on a part of their heritage and tradition.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE_HELP">
			<Text>An Encampment can only be built on flat tiles, and no two Encampments can be adjacent. It provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Encampments provide a small defense modifier to units stationed on them, and damage nearby enemy units (5) if they end their turn on or next to an Encampment. Can only be built in Shoshone territory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE]Encampment[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE_HELP">
                    <Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this Tile. Any enemy unit which ends its turn next to the Encampment takes 5 damage.</Text>
                </Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the amount of [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture provided by this tile. Removes any features on the tile. Provides a small defensive bonuse and lightly damages adjacent enemy units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN">
			<Text>Siheyuan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN_TEXT">
			<Text>A Siheyuan can only be built on flat land next to a city or next to two other Siheyuans, but cannot be built on resources. It provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Provides 1 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when worked by a city experiencing a "We Love The Empress Day".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The stately Siheyuan are a mainstay of Chinese architecture dating back to antiquity. The style is often referred to as a Chinese quadrangle, and is used from relatively dwellings and monasteries to the most grand palaces. The Forbidden City in Beijing is designed as an enormous Siheyuan. All siheyuan are positioned along a east-west axis, with the main entrance facing south. The universality of this plan allows sequential siheyuan to be arranged in long rows, creating sprawling suburbs in many of China's largest cities. The narrow alleyways between these rows of Siheyuan are known as hutongs in northern China, forming long market streets similar to middle-eastern bazaars. Recent changes in city planning and construction have resulted in many historic neighbourhoods being demolished, but there have been coordinated efforts to preserve some districts as a valuable piece of Chinese cultural identity.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN_HELP">
			<Text>A Siheyuan can only be built on flat land next to a city or next to two other Siheyuans, but cannot be built on resources. It provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Provides 1 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when worked by a city experiencing a "We Love The Empress Day".</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN]Siheyuan[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when worked by a City under "We Love The Empress Day." May only be built adjacent to a city or two Siheyuans.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Removes any features on the tile. Provides more yields when the nearby city is in a "We Love The Empress Day".</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_HORSE">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when attacking.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_IRON">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when defending.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_COAL">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Naval Units gain +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_ALUMINUM">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +5 HP when Healing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_OIL">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +2 XP after combat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_STRAT_URANIUM">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when attacking.</Text>
		</Row>


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_PRODUCTION">
			<Text>You find a cache of supplies that boost the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of your nearest city!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_GOLDEN_AGE">
			<Text>You find ancient relics that accelerate your civilization's progress towards a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_TILES">
			<Text>You find a nomadic tribe that wishes to join your Civilization, granting you additional land around the nearest City!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_CHOOSE_PRODUCTION">
			<Text>Supplies for [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in your nearest City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_CHOOSE_GOLDEN_AGE">
			<Text>Relics for [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_CHOOSE_FREE_TILES">
			<Text>A tribe that gives you land around your nearest City.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GOODY_CHOOSE_SCIENCE">
			<Text>Ancient artifacts for [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_GOLDEN_AGE_HEADING4_TITLE">
			<Text>[COLOR_GREEN]Golden Age Points[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_GOLDEN_AGE_HEADING4_BODY">
			<Text>The ruin contains relics that grant Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_GOLDEN_AGE_ADV_QUEST">
			<Text>Golden Age Points?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_PRODUCTION_HEADING4_TITLE">
			<Text>[COLOR_GREEN]Production[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_PRODUCTION_HEADING4_BODY">
			<Text>The ruin contains supplies that grant Production to your nearest city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_PRODUCTION_ADV_QUEST">
			<Text>Production?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_TILES_HEADING4_TITLE">
			<Text>[COLOR_GREEN]Tiles[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_TILES_HEADING4_BODY">
			<Text>The ruin contains settlers that grant free Tiles to your nearest city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BARBARIAN_TILES_ADV_QUEST">
			<Text>Tiles?</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_YOU_GAIN_GLOBAL">
			<Text>[COLOR_CYAN]Your current Global Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_YOU_GAIN_GLOBAL_AND_STRATEGIC">
			<Text>[COLOR_CYAN]Your current Global and Strategic Monopoly Bonuses:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_YOU_GAIN_STRATEGIC">
			<Text>[COLOR_CYAN]Your current Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_THEY_GAIN_BOTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Their current Strategic and Global Monpoly Bonuses:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_THEY_GAIN_GLOBAL">
			<Text>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Their current Global Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_THEY_GAIN_STRATEGIC">
			<Text>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Their current Strategic Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POTENTIAL">
			<Text>Potential Global Monopoly Bonus:[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_POTENTIAL_STRATEGIC">
			<Text>Potential Strategic and Global Monopoly Bonuses:[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BREAKDOWN">
			<Text>Out of {2_Total} in World:[NEWLINE]Direct control: {1_Num}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_BREAKDOWN_IMPORTS">
			<Text>Out of {2_Total} in World:[NEWLINE]Direct control: {1_Num}[NEWLINE]Import: {3_Import}[NEWLINE]From City-States: {4_CS}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_HOVER_INFO">
			<Text>(Hover over Corporation Icon or Name for details.)</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_OTHER">
			<Text>({2_CivName}) {1_Monopoly}%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EO_LOCAL_RESOURCES_CONTROLLED">
			<Text>Our Potential Monopolies</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>You control over 50% of the World's [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR], and therefore have a Global Monopoly![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>Global Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_OTHER_PLAYER_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>{3_CivName} {3_CivName: plural 1?controls; other?control;} over 50% of the World's [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR], and therefore has a Global Monopoly![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_OTHER_PLAYER_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>{2_CivName} {2_CivName: plural 1?has; other?have;} a Global Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_MONOPOLY_LOST">
			<Text>You [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]no longer have[ENDCOLOR] a Global Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]![NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lost:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_MONOPOLY_LOST">
			<Text>Lost Global Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PRODMOD_YIELD_MONOPOLY_RESOURCE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Modifier from Resource Monopoly: {1_Num}%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_HAPPINESS">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +6 Empire-Wide [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_GA_LENGTH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +25% [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Length, +2 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_GA_LENGTH_ONLY">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +30% [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Length.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_PRODUCTION">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_GOLD">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_FOOD">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +3 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_CULTURE">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_FAITH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_SCIENCE">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_PRODUCTION">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_GOLD">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_GOLD] Gold in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_FOOD">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_FOOD] Food in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_CULTURE">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_SCIENCE">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_FAITH">
			<Text>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Monopoly Bonus:[ENDCOLOR] +20% [ICON_PEACE] Faith in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Strategic Help-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_PRODUCTION_ALUMINUM">
			<Text>Used by powerful late-game Units and Buildings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +5 HP when Healing.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_GOLD_COAL">
			<Text>Used by powerful mid-game Units and Buildings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Naval Units gain +1 [ICON_MOVES] Movement.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_SCIENCE_OIL">
			<Text>Used by powerful late-game Units and Buildings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +2 XP after combat.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_YIELD_SCIENCE_HORSE">
			<Text>Used by powerful Units.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when attacking.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_PRODUCTION_IRON">
			<Text>Used by powerful Units throughout the game.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when defending.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Resource tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY_MOD_SCIENCE_URANIUM">
			<Text>Used to build terrifying weapons of mass destruction.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Strategic Monopoly Bonus (25%):[ENDCOLOR] Units gain +10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Strength when attacking.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Global Monopoly Bonus (50%):[ENDCOLOR] +10% [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in all owned Cities.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Tooltip for Strategic Monopolies -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>You control over 25% of the World's [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR], and therefore have a Strategic Monopoly![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>Strategic Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_OTHER_PLAYER_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>{3_CivName} {3_CivName: plural 1?controls; other?control;} over 25% of the World's [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR], and therefore has a Strategic Monopoly![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_OTHER_PLAYER_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_GAINED">
			<Text>{2_CivName} {2_CivName: plural 1?has; other?have;} a Strategic Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_LOST">
			<Text>You [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]no longer have[ENDCOLOR] a Strategic Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]![NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lost:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]{2_ResourceHelp}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_NOTIFICATION_SUMMARY_STRATEGIC_MONOPOLY_LOST">
			<Text>Lost Strategic Monopoly on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{1_ResourceNames}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Tooltip for Monopolies -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_FOODMOD_MONOPOLY_RESOURCE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][ICON_TRADE_WHITE] Resource Monopolies Modifier: {1_Num}%</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CULTURE_FROM_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY">
			<Text>+{1_Num}% [ICON_CULTURE] for Resource Monopolies</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_FAITH_FROM_RESOURCE_MONOPOLY">
			<Text>+{1_Num}% [ICON_PEACE] from Resource Monopolies</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MONOPOLIES_TT">
			<Text>Global Resource Monopolies are achieved when you control over 50% of a Luxury or Strategic Resource. This value can exceed 100% if you produce more of a Resource than exists on the Map. More than one Civilization can, therefore, have a Global Monopoly (though this is quite rare).</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<PostDefines>
		<Row Name="TIPI_IMPROVEMENT">
			<Key>IMPROVEMENT_ENCAMPMENT_SHOSHONE</Key>
			<Table>Improvements</Table>
		</Row>
		<Row Name="KUNA_IMPROVEMENT">
			<Key>IMPROVEMENT_KUNA</Key>
			<Table>Improvements</Table>
		</Row>
		<Row Name="EKI_IMPROVEMENT">
			<Key>IMPROVEMENT_EKI</Key>
			<Table>Improvements</Table>
		</Row>
	</PostDefines>
</GameData>
