<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 8/9/2014 4:50:23 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAUSOLEUM_HELP">
			<Text>Gain [ICON_PEACE] Faith when an owned unit is killed in battle. Bonus scales with Era. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAUSOLEUM">
			<Text>Mausoleum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAUSOLEUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Mausoleum to gain [ICON_PEACE] Faith from casualties in war. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAUSOLEUM_TEXT">
			<Text>A mausoleum is an external free-standing building constructed as a monument enclosing the interment space or burial chamber of a deceased person or people. A monument without the interment is a cenotaph. A mausoleum may be considered a type of tomb, or the tomb may be considered to be within the mausoleum. A Christian mausoleum sometimes includes a chapel.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEAVENLY_THRONE_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEAVENLY_THRONE">
			<Text>Celestial Throne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEAVENLY_THRONE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Celestial Throne for a big boost to your Holy City's base yields. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEAVENLY_THRONE_TEXT">
			<Text>A throne is the seat of state of a potentate or dignitary, especially the seat occupied by a sovereign on state occasions; or the seat occupied by a pope or bishop on ceremonial occasions. "Throne" in an abstract sense can also refer to the monarchy or the Crown itself, an instance of metonymy, and is also used in many expressions such as "the power behind the throne".</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_ALTAR_HELP">
			<Text>+15% Military Unit [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_ALTAR">
			<Text>Great Altar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_ALTAR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Great Altar for a boost to Military Unit production. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_ALTAR_TEXT">
			<Text>
				An altar is any structure upon which offerings such as sacrifices are made for religious purposes. Altars are usually found at shrines, and they can be located in temples, churches and other places of worship. Today they are used particularly in Christianity, Buddhism, Hinduism, Shinto, Taoism, as well as in Neopaganism and Ceremonial Magic. Judaism used such a structure until the destruction of the Second Temple. Many historical faiths also made use of them, including Greek and Norse religion.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIQUARY_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIQUARY">
			<Text>Reliquary</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIQUARY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Reliquary for a powerful Tourism-centric bonus. The building's Tourism bonus is only possible if all four Works of Art/Artifacts come from differing players. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIQUARY_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A reliquary is a container for relics. These may be the purported physical remains of saints, such as bones, pieces of clothing, or some object associated with saints or other religious figures. The authenticity of any given relic is often a matter of debate; for that reason, some churches require documentation of the relic's provenance. Relics have long been important to Buddhists, Christians, Hindus and many other religions. In these cultures, reliquaries are often presented in shrines, churches, or temples to which the faithful make pilgrimages in order to gain blessings. In Central West Africa, reliquaries used in the Bwete rituals contain objects considered magical, or the bones of ancestors, and are commonly constructed with a guardian figure attached to the reliquary.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_RELIQUARY_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Works of Art/Artifacts from differing players.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_RELIQUARY">
			<Text>Holy Reliquary of {2_CivAdjective}</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DIVINE_COURT_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DIVINE_COURT">
			<Text>Divine Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DIVINE_COURT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Divine Court for a boost to Gold output. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DIVINE_COURT_TEXT">
			<Text>A beth din ("house of judgment," or divine court) is a rabbinical court of Judaism. In ancient times, it was the building block of the legal system in the Biblical Land of Israel. Today, it is invested with legal powers in a number of religious matters (din Torah, "matter of litigation," plural dinei Torah) both in Israel and in Jewish communities in the Diaspora, where its judgments hold varying degrees of authority (depending upon the jurisdiction and subject matter) in matters specifically related to Jewish religious life.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SACRED_GARDEN_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SACRED_GARDEN">
			<Text>Sacred Garden</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SACRED_GARDEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Sacred Garden for a boost to Culture output. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SACRED_GARDEN_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Religion has been an important influence on garden design. Temple gardens were made in Mesopotamia and Ancient Egypt. Sacred groves were made in ancient India, Greece, Rome, China and Japan. Sacred trees were important in Celtic and Germanic Europe and still are important in India. Many groves or forests were sacred in ancient India and continue to be so in modern Hindu worship. Buddhism had a significant influence on garden design, with the Zen gardens of China and Japan as famous examples. In Christianity, particularly Catholicism and Anglicanism, Mary gardens are common among churches and institutions. The practise of creating sacred gardens is re-invigorated and adapted for modern times in the Ringing Cedars Series of books by Russian author Vladimir Megre.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOLY_COUNCIL_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOLY_COUNCIL">
			<Text>Holy Council</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOLY_COUNCIL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Holy Council for a boost to Food output. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOLY_COUNCIL_TEXT">
			<Text>An ecumenical council (or holy council) is a conference of ecclesiastical dignitaries and theological experts convened to discuss and settle matters of Church doctrine and practice in which those entitled to vote are convoked from the whole world (oikoumene) and which secures the approbation of the whole Church.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_APOSTOLIC_PALACE_HELP">
			<Text>+4 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age points. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_APOSTOLIC_PALACE">
			<Text>Apostolic Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_APOSTOLIC_PALACE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Apostolic Palace for more rapid Golden Ages. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_APOSTOLIC_PALACE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Latin word basilica has three distinct applications in modern English. The word was originally used to describe an open, Roman, public court building, usually located adjacent to the forum of a Roman town. By extension it was applied to Christian buildings of the same form and continues to be used in an architectural sense to describe those buildings with a central nave and aisles. Later, the term came to refer specifically to a large and important church, the Apostolic Palace, that has been given special ceremonial rights by the Pope.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRAND_OSSUARY_HELP">
			<Text>May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRAND_OSSUARY">
			<Text>Grand Ossuary</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRAND_OSSUARY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build the Ossuary for lots of Faith. Constructing this National Wonder will also allow you to choose a Reformation Belief. May only be constructed in a Holy City, and only if at least 20% of the global population follows your Religion. Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Division.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRAND_OSSUARY_TEXT">
			<Text>An ossuary is a chest, box, building, well, or site made to serve as the final resting place of human skeletal remains. They are frequently used where burial space is scarce. A body is first buried in a temporary grave, then after some years the skeletal remains are removed and placed in an ossuary. The greatly reduced space taken up by an ossuary means that it is possible to store the remains of many more people in a single tomb than if the original coffins were left as is. In Persia, the Zoroastrians used a deep well for this function from the earliest times (circa 3,000 years ago) and called it astudan (literally, "the place for the bones"). There are many rituals and regulations in the Zoroastrian faith concerning the astudans. Among the pre-7th-century Sogdians in the region of central Asia, the name for an ossuary was tanbar.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>