<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- America -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDEPENDENCE_HALL">
			<Text>Independence Hall</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDEPENDENCE_HALL_HELP">
			<Text>Unlocks access to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Slater Mill[ENDCOLOR], [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]West Point[ENDCOLOR], and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Smithsonian Institute[ENDCOLOR] in the [COLOR_CYAN]Industrial Era[ENDCOLOR].
				[NEWLINE]Possible Theming Bonuses:
  				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +8 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_ART] Great Works of Art.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDEPENDENCE_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>Originally constructed as the state house of Pennsylvannia, Independence Hall is where the United States Declaration of Independence and Constitution were debated and formally adopted, making it the birthplace of the American nation. Today, Independence Hall is a museum and the centre of the Independence National Park in the heart of Philadelphia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDEPENDENCE_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Make sure to build it before you gain the next Policy, to benefit from the unique 5% Policy cost reduction at the first occasion. The Culture bonuses are the same as that of The Royal Collection, but it lacks any Theming requirements, so place any Great Works of Art in the slots. Additionally, it reduces Boredom by 1 in all cities. In short, constructing The Independence Hall is a priority.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Unlocks the ability for America to build 1 of 3 unique wonders in the Industrial Era. Choose which wonder is the best for you early to arrange you technology research order accordingly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_INDEPENDENCEHALL">
			<Text>National Treasures</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_INDEPENDENCE_HALL_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Art from your Civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMITHSONIAN_INSTITUTION">
			<Text>Smithsonian Institution</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMITHSONIAN_INSTITUTION_TEXT">
			<Text>The Smithsonian Institution, originally established in 1846 as the United States National Museum is a group of museums and research centers administered by the Government of the United States. Lovingly called "the nation's attic" for its eclectic holdings of 138 million items, the Institution's nineteen museums, nine research centers, and zoo include historical and architectural landmarks, mostly located in the District of Columbia. Additional facilities are located in Arizona, Maryland, Massachusetts, New York City, Virginia, and Panama. A further 170 museums are Smithsonian Affiliates. The Institution's thirty million annual visitors are admitted without charge; funding comes from the Institution's endowment, private, corporate, and government contributions, membership dues, as well as retail, concession and licensing revenues. Institution publications include Smithsonian and Air and Space magazines.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMITHSONIAN_INSTITUTION_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMITHSONIAN_INSTITUTION_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of the three mutually exclusive Wonders that America can build after it has completed Independence Hall. Choose your destiny carefully.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Note that all 3 Wonders have symmetry between them, focusing either on [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, or [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in similar ways. Thus, which Yield and Victory type you care most about should influence your choice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Build the Smithsonian Institution if you aim for the Cultural or Scientific victory. Your Cities receive extra [ICON_CULTURE] Culture based on their [ICON_GOLD] Gold output, which lets you unlock Policies faster. Focusing on [ICON_GOLD] Gold per turn is a strong strategy from now on. This wonder synergizes best with Artistry as this Policy Branch lets you create more Great Works or Landmarks that gain a [ICON_RESEARCH] Science bonus from this Wonder. Freedom Ideology will further benefit Landmarks and Tourism output.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Museums and Research Labs gain powerful yields, so it's worth building them as soon as possible.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Since it's unlocked at Archaeology, you will reveal antiquity sites early, so consider expanding near unowned sites to create Landmarks in your new territories. They are recommended over Great Works because on top of the bigger [ICON_RESEARCH] Science bonus, they provide [ICON_GOLD] Gold which feeds back to the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture bonus. However, keep your City number in check to avoid the [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism penalty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The 25% discount on tile [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchases promotes buying tiles liberally to boost prodution of important Buildings, Wonders or Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEST_POINT">
			<Text>West Point</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEST_POINT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEST_POINT_TEXT">
			<Text>The United States Military Academy, informally known as West Point, is the oldest service academy, educating cadets to become commissioned officers for the United States Army. The academy is notable for producing some of the most renowned generals in modern history in addition to numerous heads of state, both foreign and domestic. The campus is the oldest continuously operating American army post, originally built as a river fort to overlook and control shipping along the Hudson River. As a result, the campus is a national landmark, dotted with numerous monuments and statues representing its long and storied history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEST_POINT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of the three mutually exclusive Wonders that America can build after it has completed Independence Hall. Choose your destiny carefully.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Note that all 3 Wonders have symmetry between them, focusing either on [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, or [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in similar ways. Thus, which Yield and Victory type you care most about should influence your choice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Build West Point if you aim for the Scientific or Domination Victory. Your Cities receive extra [ICON_RESEARCH] Science based on their [ICON_GOLD] Gold output, which lets you unlock Techonologies faster and therefore also helps with gaining a military advantage. Focusing on [ICON_GOLD] Gold per turn is a strong strategy from now on. Moreover, Splash I is a strong Promotion that is given to all Siege and Naval Ranged Units, so if you plan to war, consider this Wonder more. Despite Splash I is given to Siege units, Minutemen are so strong that they shouldn't be replaced in attacking enemy Units in any way. West Point benefits most from Fealty which encourages wide empires, because such an empire is needed both for Scientific and Domination victories. Both Rationalism and Industry fit too, by multiplying [ICON_RESEARCH] Science yields from the Buildings and boosting [ICON_GOLD] Gold generation respectively.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Military Academies and Arsenals gain powerful yields so it's worth building them as soon as possible.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Since it's unlocked at Military Science, try to focus on this Technology first, and at that point why not build Brandenburg Gate as well if you can?[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The 25% discount on tile [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchases promotes buying tiles liberally to boost prodution of important Buildings, Wonders or Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLATER_MILL">
			<Text>Slater Mill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLATER_MILL_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLATER_MILL_TEXT">
			<Text>A National Historic Landmark, the Slater Mill is located next to the Blackstone River in Pawtucket, Rhode Island. Modeled after cotton spinning mills first established in England, the Slater Mill is the first water-powered cotton spinning mill in North America to utilize the Arkwright system of cotton spinning as developed by Richard Arkwright. Samuel Slater, the mill's founder, apprenticed as a young man in Belper, England with industrialist Jedediah Strutt. Shortly after immigrating to the United States, Slater was hired by Moses Brown of Providence, Rhode Island to produce a working set of machines necessary to spin cotton yarn using water-power. Construction of the machines, as well as a dam, waterway, waterwheel and mill was completed in 1793. Manufacturing was based on Richard Arkwright's cotton spinning system which included carding, drawing, and spinning machines. Slater initially hired children and families to work in his mill, establishing a pattern that was replicated throughout the Blackstone Valley and known as the "Rhode Island System". It was later eclipsed by Francis Cabot Lowell's Waltham System. Slater Mill was the first property to be listed on the National Register of Historic Places, and was designated a National Historic Landmark on November 13, 1966.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SLATER_MILL_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of the three mutually exclusive Wonders that America can build after it has completed Independence Hall. Choose your destiny carefully.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Note that all 3 Wonders have symmetry between them, focusing either on [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, or [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in similar ways. Thus, which Yield and Victory type you care most about should influence your choice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Build the Slater Mill if you aim for the Diplomatic or Domination victory. Your Cities receive extra [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production based on their [ICON_GOLD] Gold output, which lets you build Military and Diplomatic Units faster. The [ICON_RESEARCH] Science or [ICON_CULTURE] Culture that the alternatives provide is stronger, unless you heavily lack [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. The West Point encourages Domination too, and it's usually a better choice, especially if you're lacking in [ICON_RESEARCH] Science but your [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production capacity is strong. Otherwise the Slater Mill might be better. Focusing on [ICON_GOLD] Gold per turn is a strong strategy from now on. This Wonder synergizes best with Statecraft as this Policy Branch helps with allying city states and gaining Congress Votes, and gives an extra Trade Route. Industry and Freedom will further add Trade Routes which are important, because with the Slater Mill's 25% shorter Trade Route duration, you will be able to establish your Franchises faster.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Factories and Stock Exchanges gain powerful yields so it's worth building them as soon as possible.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The 25% discount on tile [ICON_GOLD] Gold purchases promotes buying tiles liberally to boost prodution of important Buildings, Wonders or Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_AMERICA_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"My country 'tis of thee,[NEWLINE]Sweet land of liberty.[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - Samuel F. Smith[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOMESTEAD">
			<Text>Homestead</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOMESTEAD_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOMESTEAD_TEXT">
			<Text>A Homestead is a complex of buildings on a large landholding, typically a ranch, settled in accordance with the United States Homesteading Acts. The US Government implemented a policy of "free soil", allowing claimants, effectively squatters, ownership of land which they had converted into productive farms or ranches. Nearly 10% of the continental United States was settled in this way; 270 million acres of land claimed by approximately 1.6 million homesteaders between 1862 and 1930.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The colonization of vast swathes of the continental interior left an indelible mark on the American psyche. Legends of the frontier, the Old West, Cowboys and Indians still permeate American culture, informing their sense of independence, enterprising spirit and mastery over nature.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOMESTEAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONITOR">
			<Text>Monitor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONITOR_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONITOR_TEXT">
			<Text>In the Civil War, a "monitor" was an armored, steam-driven warship with a very low freeboard (as a foot from waterline to deck) mounting a few heavy guns in one or more turrets. Intended primarily for use on the rivers that cut through Southern territory, the unseaworthy craft were used to support land forces, protect riverbank positions, and control river passage; monitors were crucial to the Union victories in the West, notably along the Mississippi River.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONITOR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Monitor benefits a lot from Combat Strength boosts and Dauntless Promotion, becauce the combined -8 Damage Reduction works better the less damage enemies can deal to you. Therefore, promote your Monitors as much as you can and accompany them with Great Admirals. The City Defense Bonus is a small benefit; the main strength of this Ship lies in its high base Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Arabia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIMARISTAN">
			<Text>Bimaristan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIMARISTAN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIMARISTAN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Bimaristan were centers for medical treatment, the precursor to the modern Hospital. The Arab world was notable for several medical practices which have become commonplace today including separating patients by their ailments into wards, the development of patient medical records, the secularization of medical care, and standards for medical practitioners, including examinations and licensing. Bimaristans were paid for by charitable endowments called Waqfs. This guaranteed that the operations and cost of treatment would be borne by the institution, regardless of the patient's race, religion, gender, or social standing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIMARISTAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HASHEMITE_RAIDER">
			<Text>Hashemite Raider</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_TEXT">
			<Text>Long considered the "Sick Man of Europe", Ottoman power was in decline well before nationalist sentiment took root in the Arab population. When WWI broke out among the European powers the Ottomans set about crushing Arab dissent. Arab citizens responded in a popular revolt, declaring a new Islamic empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Hussein bin Ali, Sharif of Mecca, began the rebellion in hopes of re-establishing a Hashemite dynasty in Arabia, and led his fellow Arabs in armed rebellion against their Turkish masters in Hejaz. Seeing an opportunity to tie down Ottoman forces in a new front, the British promised to recognize Arab hegemony and heavily subsidize the revolt, sending the now famous T.E. Lawrence as a liaison. With this new infusion of funds and equipment, the Arabs waged a guerilla war through the desert, crippling Ottoman supply lines. With the help of French and English navy, they were able to take several ports along the Mediterranean coast, emboldening even more to join their cause.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]With the end of WWI in 1918 and the Ottomans' defeat, the Arabs expected the full cooperation of their European allies as they established their new kingdom. However, the English and French had other plans. Behind closed doors, the French and English secretly formed the Sykes-Picot Agreement which divided the Middle-East amongst their own respective spheres of influence. This gross betrayal of a trusted ally has soured relations between the Arab states and the West ever since.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HASHEMITE_RAIDER_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Assyria -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_ROYAL_LIBRARY">
			<Text>Knowledge from Around the World</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROYAL_LIBRARY_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure all three Great Works are from foreign Civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAMASSU_GATE">
			<Text>Lamassu Gate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAMASSU_GATE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAMASSU_GATE_TEXT">
			<Text>Lamassu are Assyrian protective deities, often depicted as having a human head, the body of a bull or lion, and bird's wings. The Lamassu were household protective spirits of Babylonian and Assyrian commoners, and were later adopted as royal protectors. Depictions of Lamassu are found throughout Assyrian architecture, positioned as sentinels at the thresholds of buildings and as colossal statues on each side of the city and palace gates. Common folk, for their part, engraved Lamassi onto clay tablets and buried them under their doors' threshold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LAMASSU_GATE_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IRON_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Iron Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IRON_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IRON_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>Before horses were bred to be big enough to carry men on their backs, Assyrian chariots were used to smash into and disperse enemy formations. These sturdy chariots were both a platform for archers and javelineers and a weapon in their own right, forming the first shock tactics of history. Recognizing the great value of horses as tools of war, Assyrians conquered portions of Media specifically for their esteemed horse lineages.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_IRON_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Austria -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHUTZENSTAND">
			<Text>Schützenstand</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHUTZENSTAND_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHUTZENSTAND_TEXT">
			<Text>The Standschützen were originally rifle guilds and companies that had been formed in the 15th and 16th centuries within the Austrian county of Tyrol. A Standschütze was an enrolled member of a Schützenstand ("shooting club"), which automatically committed him to the voluntary military protection of the state of Tyrol and Vorarlberg. In effect this made Standschützen a Tyrolean local militia and home guard.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Standschützen were periodically called upon to defend their homeland from rebellions and invasions, but their actions in World War I were particularly distinguished. Italy entered late into the war against Austria and opened a new front through the Alpine passes of Tyrol. The Austrians had already committed battalions of Tyrolean recruits elsewhere upon the war's initial outbreak, so the Standschützen consisting of young, elderly, and injured men were called upon to defend their province with little notice or material support. Despite this, the Standschützen fought valiantly in defense of their homes and repulsed the Italians for weeks until regular troops could arrive. It is without a doubt that the actions of the Standschützen saved Autria a devastating loss against a fresh invasion by an opportunistic foe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHUTZENSTAND_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BALLHAUSPLATZ">
			<Text>Ballhausplatz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BALLHAUSPLATZ_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BALLHAUSPLATZ_TEXT">
			<Text>Ballhausplatz is a square in central Vienna containing the building (with the address Ballhausplatz 2) that for over two hundred years has been the official residence of the most senior Austrian Cabinet Minister, the State Chancellor, today the Chancellor of Austria (Prime Minister). As a result, Ballhausplatz is often used as shorthand for the Austrian Federal Chancellery. Until 1918 the Foreign Ministry of Austria-Hungary was also housed here. Similar to Downing Street or the Hotel Matignon, the word Ballhausplatz (or Ballplatz for short) is a synecdoche for the seat of power.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BALLHAUSPLATZ_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GRENZER">
			<Text>Grenzer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GRENZER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GRENZER_TEXT">
			<Text>The Habsburgs' military frontier were composed of a diverse array of client duchies, soldier-settlers, and refugees. These border-men, or Grenzers, developed a fearsome reputation for vigilance, tenacity, and fieldcraft after generations defending their lands from Ottoman raids. When the Muslim threat subsided in the 18th century, the Grenzers became a mainstay of Austro-Hungarian forces in their European conflicts, distinguishing themselves as flexible and reliable infantry in the Napoleonic Wars.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GRENZER_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Aztec -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELPOCHCALLI">
			<Text>Telpochcalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELPOCHCALLI_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELPOCHCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>The Telpochcalli, meaning "House of the Young Men" were centers of education for Aztec youth. While the children of nobles went to a separate institution called the Calmecac, the Telpochcalli were open to all Aztec boys starting at age 15, making them one of the earliest examples of public education in history. Education in Aztec society focused on civics, warfare, and religion. Accounts of the experience of growing up going to a Telpochcalli describe an austere and strict environment, where boys were expected to grow their own food on collective farms and were given responsibilities such as maintaining and repairing public facilities like temples.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELPOCHCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUEY_TEOCALLI">
			<Text>Huey Teocalli</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUEY_TEOCALLI_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUEY_TEOCALLI_TEXT">
			<Text>In the Aztec Empire, a teocalli was a terraced pyramid surmounted by a roofed temple, and acted as the site of all the important religious rituals in the town. The greatest of these teocalli was located in the heart of Tenochtitlan, the Huey Teocalli (or, according to the Spanish, the Templo Mayor) dedicated to a pair of gods: Huitzilopochtli, the god of war, and Tlaloc, the god of agriculture (an indication of what was important in Aztec culture). Each god had a separate temple, reached by separate staircases.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUEY_TEOCALLI_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTOMI">
			<Text>Otomi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTOMI_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTOMI_TEXT">
			<Text>The Otomi are an ancient people from the Altiplano region, predate the Mexica's arrival there by thousands of years. The name Otomi is Nahuatl, meaning "One who walks with Arrows" in recognition of their strength and bravery in combat. Within the Triple-Alliance, Otomi became a name for a military society, perhaps because of the fearsome reputation of the Otomi people or because they were originally comprised of Otomi allies and mercenaries. Whatever the case, the use of Otomi both as the name of an ethnicity within the Aztec Empire and as a military faction makes it hard to discern which is which in the historical record.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OTOMI_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Babylon -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SABUM_KIBITUM">
			<Text>Sabum Kibitum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SABUM_KIBITUM_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SABUM_KIBITUM_TEXT">
			<Text>The Babylonians were descended from semi-nomadic Amorite and Akkadian tribes from upper Mesopotamia. With the collapse of the Sumerian and Akkadian kingdoms, these Amorite tribes poured into Mesopotamia unopposed and established new dynasties. While in many respects these conquerors assimilated into Sumerian culture, their armies retained the toughness of their nomadic roots.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Sabum Kibitum were the heavy troops of the Babylonians and one of the earliest examples of career soldiers in history. Assembled from the royal guard and city residents, Sabum Kibitum were armed with long and short spears, javelins and bows to form a disciplined and flexible fighting force.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SABUM_KIBITUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETEMENANKI">
			<Text>Etemenanki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETEMENANKI_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETEMENANKI_TEXT">
			<Text>Etemenanki was the Ziggurat of Marduk, god of storms and head of the Babylonian pantheon. Ziggurats were religious temples erected in Mesopotamian cities as the literal homes for the city's patron god. It was believed that the gods originally lived in the high mountains, so Ziggurats took the form of artificial mountains inside the city to make their resident god feel more comfortable.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ETEMENANKI_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Brazil -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BANDEIRANTE">
			<Text>Bandeirante</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BANDEIRANTE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Bandeirantes ("those who carry the flag") were 17th-century Portuguese settlers in Brazil and fortune hunters. They led expeditions called bandeiras ("flags") which penetrated the interior of Brazil far south and west of the Tordesillas Line of 1494, which officially divided the Castilian or later Spanish (west) domain from the Portuguese (east) domain in South America. Though they originally aimed to capture and force Indigenous Americans into slavery, the bandeirantes later began to focus their expeditions on finding gold, silver, and diamond mines. As they ventured into unmapped regions in search of profit and adventure, they expanded the effective borders of the Brazilian colony.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BANDEIRANTE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Avoid exploring early game (within reason) to leave lots of unexplored territory for the Bandeirantes, so that they can grant you enormous amounts of [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture by revealing tiles. For reference, exploring 60% of a standard map will yield approximately 10,000 of each yield. These yields are added to the nearest owned city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Bandeirante is faster, heals every turn, and doesn't use Movement for pillaging, so use it for this, but carefully. During peace, after you have explored the World, use them to build Mines, Quarries, Brazilwood Camps, and Forts in your frontier Cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BANDEIRANTE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMBRAPA">
			<Text>Embrapa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMBRAPA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMBRAPA_TEXT">
			<Text>Embrapa is a state-owned research corporation affiliated with the Brazilian Ministry of Agriculture. Since its inception on April 26, 1973, it has been devoted to developing technologies, knowledge and technical-scientific information aimed at Brazilian agriculture, including livestock. Embrapa's organizational structure is composed of 46 centers that can be divided into Research Units or Service Units, and of 17 Central Units that comprise the corporation's headquarters. Such research centers are distributed throughout the country in nearly all Brazilian states.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMBRAPA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>When aiming for Cultural Victory, Embrapa is a must due to the extra [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism from the City's [ICON_FOOD] Food output. [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism is a yield that is hard to come by, so focusing more on [ICON_FOOD] Food generation might be beneficial to take full advantage of this. Research Plastics to unlock this building as soon as possible.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When not aiming for Cultural or Science Victories, building Embrapa is still worth due to the strong bonuses to [ICON_RESEARCH] Science which are always valuable, especially in Cities with many Forest or Jungle tiles and Farm resources, as these gain significant yields. In Cities without these tiles, Embrapa loses significance, so you may wish to delay its construction. In any case, working all the tiles strengthened by Embrapa is highly recommended.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AMAZONAS">
			<Text>Amazonas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AMAZONAS_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AMAZONAS_TEXT">
			<Text>The Amazonas was a large steam frigate serving as the flagship of the Brazilian Navy during the Paraguayan War, the bloodiest conflict in South American history. The hulking warship played a pivotal roll at the Battle of Riachuelo, where a combined artillery and naval brigade of Paraguayans attempted to ambush the Brazilians in the early morning and under the cover of a dense fog. Caught by surprise, the Brazilians were put at a great disadvantage, but rallied and countered the Paraguayans. The Amazonas proved to be the decisive factor, ramming and sinking two ships and disabling a third. At Riachuelo, the Paraguayans navy was badly damaged, putting a halt to their momentum for the remainder of the war. Brazil and its allies took the initiative and maintained naval supremacy for the remainder of the war.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_AMAZONAS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Thanks to the Blitz Promotion, Amazonas not only can attack twice per turn, but can also move after attacking. This enables focus attacks on ships, which is strong as it allows to defeat enemy Units more reliably. This synergizes with Amazonas' gain of Golden Age Points and Great Admiral Points upon defeating enemy Units which further synergizes with Brazil's Unique Ability. Blitz also allows attacking Cities with many ships in a single turn, which stopped being possible with the obsolation of Galleasses. Consider building many Amazonas and performing mass sieges on Cities with as many of them as possible, even without siege promotions from the Hull Promotion line!</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Byzantium -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TETRACONCH">
			<Text>Tetraconch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TETRACONCH_TEXT">
			<Text>Over many centuries, Byzantine architecture gradually drifted away from older Roman forms. Byzantine-style buildings are often noted for their high domes and intricate mosaic work, and far greater use of stone and brick construction. The tetraconch churches, meaning "four shells" in Greek, represent the highest achievement of Byzantine architecture. The floorplan of these buildings incorporates four domed apses, giving the building the shape of a cross, with the central space capped by a high dome. The form was widely used in mausoleums and baptisteries and informed later Ottoman and Renaissance architectural traditions that followed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TETRACONCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for every 3 Citizens bonus is very strong, so having high Population is encouraged. It will significantly increase your total Faith generation, so consider your Beliefs and Policies knowing you will have a lot of Faith to spend. For example, Zealotry might be an atypical but very strong choice for Byzantium. With the +100% Religious Pressure added to Cities receiving a Trade Route, consider which owned or foreign Cities need more Religious Pressure when choosing Trade Route destinations. Due to having no gold maintenance, extra Culture, and the above bonuses, this Building should be a priority.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TETRACONCH_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_APLEKTON">
			<Text>Aplekton</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_APLEKTON_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Byzantine replacement for the Fort.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile, and it cannot be [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]stolen[ENDCOLOR] by foreign Empires. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it. Has improved yields compared to the Fort it replaces, including [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_APLEKTON_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_APLEKTON_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Aplekton, from the Latin 'applicatum', was a Byzantine term used in the 10th-14th centuries for a fortified army base (in this sense similar to the Greek metaton). The aplekta were major assembly areas, where stores of supplies were kept and where the provincial armies of the themata were to join the main imperial force for a campaign. The original construction dates most probably to the reign of Emperor Constantine V (r. 741–775). Emperor Constantine VII Porphyrogennetos (r. 945–959), in his treatise on imperial expeditions, records the aplekta from west to east as follows: Malagina, Dorylaion, Kaborkin, Koloneia, Kaisareia and Dazimon.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_APLEKTON">
			<Text>Build an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_APLEKTON]Aplekton[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_APLEKTON_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile, and it cannot be [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]stolen[ENDCOLOR] by foreign Empires. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_APLEKTON_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE_LOCAL] Border Growth Points, and defend the tile.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Carthage -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON">
			<Text>Great Cothon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_TEXT">
			<Text>A cothon is an artificial, protected inner harbor such as that in Carthage during the Punic Wars around 200 BC. The cothon at Carthage was divided into a rectangular merchant harbor followed by an inner protected harbor reserved for military use only. This inner harbor was circular and surrounded by an outer ring of structures divided into a series of docking bays for ship maintenance, along with an island structure at its centre that also housed navy ships. Each individual docking bay featured a raised slipway. Above the raised docking bays was a second level consisting of warehouses where oars and rigging were kept along with supplies such as wood and canvas. On the island structure there existed a raised 'cabin' where the admiral in command could observe the whole harbor along with the surrounding sea. Altogether the inner docking complex could house up to 220 ships. The entire harbor was protected by an outer wall and the main entrance could be closed off with iron chains.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Maximizing the amount of Trade Routes is a prority for Carthage because their bonus to Trade Route [ICON_GOLD] Gold generation from Resource Diversity makes them much more profitable. Since the Great Cothon grants 2 additional Trade Routes and many other strong bonuses, this Wonder is an absolute priority, especially since it's unlocked earlier at Currency.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Build it in the City with the highest amount of unique Luxury Resources as it is the main determinant of the profitability of your Trade Routes and like the Chartered Company, the Great Cothon further increases this bonus for the City in which it is built, and grants an additional copy of each of these Resources. This City should become your main sender of Trade Routes.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As this National Wonder grants [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to all Lighthouses and Harbors and grants free Harbors to all coastal Cities, it is strongly encouraged to settle coastal Cities over landlocked ones.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASAMU">
			<Text>Asamu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASAMU_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASAMU_TEXT">
			<Text>In contrast to most Phoenician colonies, Carthage grew larger and more quickly thanks to its combination of favorable climate, arable land, and lucrative trade routes. Within just one century of its founding, its population rose to 30,000. Though the specific date and circumstances are unknown, Carthage became independent in the middle of the 6th century BC. It had grown into a fully independent thalassocracy, embarking its own colonization efforts across the western Mediterranean. Carthage became an expansionist power, driven by its desire to access new sources of wealth and trade. By 300 BC, through its vast patchwork of colonies, vassals, and satellite states, held together by its naval dominance of the western and central Mediterranean Sea, Carthage controlled the largest territory in the region, including the coast of northwestern Africa, southern and eastern Iberia, and the islands of Sicily, Sardinia, Corsica, Malta, and the Balearic Islands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ASAMU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Asamu allows for more aggressive settling, but requires very high [ICON_GOLD] Gold generation, as it cannot be produced but only be purchased for a lot of [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Because purchasing one doesn't decrease Population like producing a Settler does, a major bottleneck on the speed of settling early game is replaced by [ICON_GOLD] Gold generation. Therefore, consider gathering as much [ICON_GOLD] Gold as possible early game from your Unique Ability, destroying Barbarian Encampments, exploring Ancient Ruins, and working [ICON_GOLD] Gold tiles to then settle at a high pace. Because Asamu can retreat from melee attack once per turn, it can travel though barbarain terriory without escort, unless two Units can attack it. Additionally, since Asamu can embark without having the Fishing Technology, you can claim valuable islands before your rivals. You can couple that with producing Settlers at the same time. This way, you can secure many great City locations with many Luxury Resources, synergizing with your Unique Ability.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Celts -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CEILIDH_HALL_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SCYTHED_CHARIOT">
			<Text>Scythed Chariot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_TEXT">
			<Text>Scythed chariots are modified war chariots with long blades extending from the wheel axels. Though often dismissed as fanciful storytelling, the use of scythed chariots has been ascribed to Pictish, Irish and Iceni armies. The only report of a scythed chariot in Britain outside of Roman propaganda comes from the Irish Ulster Cycle, during the adventures of Chu Chulainn.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Although chariots had fallen out of use in continental Europe from the end of the 3rd century BC, Caesar found that they remained significant in British warfare. Caesar encountered both Celtic cavalry and chariots and described how these warriors would throw javelins from their vehicles before dismounting to fight on foot. Celtic soldiers could return to their chariots to quickly retreat or redeploy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"They make war not only on horseback but also from two horse chariots and cars armed in the Gallic fashion - they call them Covinni - on which they use axles equipped with scythes."[NEWLINE][TAB]- Pomponius Mela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SCYTHED_CHARIOT_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Oppidum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Celtic Great Person Tile Improvement. Can be built by Great Engineers, Merchants, Scientists, and Generals. Boosts all these Great People's Missions by a reduced amount. Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE]Improves Strategic Resources. Provides various yields and +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to Units stationed on it. Improves Adjacent Tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OPPIDUM_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OPPIDUM_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An Oppidum is a large defended settlement associated with the late La Tene culture. These fortified villages were often built in naturally protected areas and full of circular constructions. In times of conflict, the people who lived in open fields moved to these strategically located compounds to ensure their safety. Oppida could also have other purposes such as control of territory or safeguarding of crops. The most famous oppidum was Alesia, the site of the battle between Julius Caesar and Vercingetorix and the final defeat of the Gauls, ending of Gallic independence in France and Belgium.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OPPIDUM">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CELTS_OPPIDUM]Oppidum[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OPPIDUM_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built next to another Oppidum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Constructing the Oppidum will increase the yields of [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER], [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT], and [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Missions (by a reduced amount compared to their own Great Person Tile Improvements), and will consume this unit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defense Bonus to units stationed on it. Provides bonus yields to all adjacent Tiles.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- China -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN">
			<Text>Siheyuan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The stately Siheyuan are a mainstay of Chinese architecture dating back to antiquity. The style is often referred to as a Chinese quadrangle, and is used from relatively dwellings and monasteries to the most grand palaces. The Forbidden City in Beijing is designed as an enormous Siheyuan. All siheyuan are positioned along a east-west axis, with the main entrance facing south. The universality of this plan allows sequential siheyuan to be arranged in long rows, creating sprawling suburbs in many of China's largest cities. The narrow alleyways between these rows of Siheyuan are known as hutongs in northern China, forming long market streets similar to middle-eastern bazaars. Recent changes in city planning and construction have resulted in many historic neighbourhoods being demolished, but there have been coordinated efforts to preserve some districts as a valuable piece of Chinese cultural identity.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built on flat land adjacent to a city or next to two other Siheyuans. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when worked by a city during [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]We Love The Empress Day[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SIHEYUAN]Siheyuan[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when worked by a City during [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]We Love The Empress Day[ENDCOLOR]. Can only be built on flat land tiles adjacent to a city or two Siheyuans.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SIHEYUAN_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science when worked by a city during [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]We Love The Empress Day[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EXAMINATION_HALL">
			<Text>Examination Hall</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EXAMINATION_HALL_TEXT">
			<Text>Perhaps the greatest legacy of Chinese culture is the Imperial Examination system with which the Son of Heaven's empire was staffed with civil servants for over two millennia. The Imperial examinations represented an attempt to create an aristocracy of learning, a remarkable advance over the warrior and hereditary aristocracies that dominated the rest of the world. Amounting to tests of rote memorization, the examinations required direct quotations of Confucian philosophy and ethics from the Five Confucian Classics. A scholar who obtained the highest degree, the jinshi, would have his memory trained to a tremendous degree.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As Western universities began to move away from their own classical tradition to embrace economics, engineering and natural science, China's scholarly efforts languished in the ancient literary past. Under pressure to modernize, the examinations were abolished in 1890 by Dowager Empress Cixi, leaving behind a legacy as the first system of intellectual meritocracy the world had ever seen.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"We tried an experiment which is unique in the history of the world: We sought to rule this great country not by force, but by wisdom. And for centuries we succeeded."[NEWLINE][TAB]- Anonymous Confucian Philosopher; excerpt from "On a Chinese Screen"</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EXAMINATION_HALL_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EXAMINATION_HALL_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TREASURE_SHIP">
			<Text>Treasure Ship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TREASURE_SHIP_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TREASURE_SHIP_TEXT">
			<Text>The Xiafan Guanjun (lit. "The Foreign Expeditionary Armada") was the great treasure fleet of the Ming Dynasty. At the behest of Emperor Zhu Di, the legendary admiral Zheng He headed seven voyages between 1405 and 1433 AD. The Xiafan Guanjun ranged as far as the Arabian Peninsula in their task of projecting Chinese influence abroad, bringing many smaller nations under the suzerainty of China.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Xiafan Guanjun had some of the largest wooden ships ever constructed, called Baochuan (lit. "Treasure Ship"), measuring up to 416 feet in length. It would be another century before European ships could match the size and power of China's fleet, making China the undisputed naval superpower of the 15th century. Despite their superiority, Zheng He's voyages were primarily diplomatic, bringing envoys and even kings before the emperor to present tribute and perform the 'kowtow', a ritual act of reverence and subservience.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"As an engine for carrying man and his commerce upon the high and stormy seas as well as on the vast inland waterways, it is doubtful if any class of vessel… is more suited or better adapted to its purpose than the Chinese or Indian junk, and it is certain that for flatness of sail and handiness, the Chinese rig is unsurpassed."[NEWLINE][TAB]- H. Warington Smyth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TREASURE_SHIP_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Denmark -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE">
			<Text>Runestone</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE_TEXT">
			<Text>A runestone is typically a raised stone with a runic inscription, but the term can also be applied to inscriptions on boulders and on bedrock. The tradition began in the 4th century and lasted into the 12th century, but most of the runestones date from the late Viking Age. Most runestones are located in Scandinavia, but there are also scattered runestones in locations that were visited by Norsemen during the Viking Age. Runestones are often memorials to dead men. Runestones were usually brightly coloured when erected, though this is no longer evident as the colour has worn off.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Danish replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIGHTHOUSE}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIGHTHOUSE}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE} produces [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when units from this City pillage tiles (Roads and Railroads do not count), generates more [ICON_FOOD] Food from ocean tiles, and increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of melee land and naval units. Unlike the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIGHTHOUSE}, the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RUNESTONE} can be built in a non-coastal city.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE">
			<Text>Andelsbevægelse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Andelsbevægelse was a Danish Cooperative Movement, corporations where individual members each owned a share in the risks and profits of the collective. Co-ops, as they are commonly referred to, continue to be popular in the farming industry as a way of mitigating bad harvests on the part of a few members.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After the disastrous Second War of Schleswig where Denmark lost considerable territory, Denmark began to reclaim moors in central and western Jutland for farming. Shortly after, the rapidly industrializing United States began pouring exports of grain into Denmark's biggest customer, Great Britain, tanking the prices for Denmark's produce. With the livelihoods of many Danish farmers at risk, they formed a new strategy to switch from grain products to dairy and meat.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This shift in Danish agriculture was full of uncertainty, requiring that farmers form the Andelsbevægelse to share in the risks. By the time prices for grain had finally stabilized, Danish agriculture had completely changed. Dairies and slaughterhouses dotted the landscape; now they were IMPORTING grain from Russia to feed their livestock!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ANDELSBEVAEGELSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LONGSHIP">
			<Text>Longship</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LONGSHIP_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LONGSHIP_TEXT">
			<Text>Longships were a type of boat invented and used by the Norsemen for trade, exploration, and warfare during the Viking Age. The longship's design evolved over many centuries, beginning in the Stone Age with the invention of the umiak and continuing up until the 6th century with clinker-built ships like Nydam and Kvalsund, appearing in its complete form between the 9th and 13th centuries. They were all made out of wood, with woven wool sails, and had numerous details and carvings on the hull.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Longships were notable for their quick speed and light construction. The ships were sturdy and reliable at sea, yet light enough to be carried onto shore or even tipped over as a makeshift shelter. The ability to move quickly in and out of shore was invaluable during the Vikings' infamous raids.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The character and appearance of these ships are still reflected in Scandinavian boat-building traditions. Skills and methods for making longships are still used worldwide, often with modern adaptations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LONGSHIP_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Egypt -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAMLUK">
			<Text>Mamluk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAMLUK_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAMLUK_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mamluks were a military knightly caste composed of slave-soldiers captured as young boys and sold into the Arabic world to serve as retainers. Because of their slave status ('Mamluk' directly translates to possession), these young men were dependent on their lord for social status and career advancement, making them reliable and dependable institutions in the Fatimid and Ayyubid dynasties of Cairo. The Mamluks were renowned warriors for their defense of Islam from waves of Crusader and Mongol invasions. In some cases, the Mamluks rose up and secured their own dynasties, initiating sultanates in Egypt, India, and Iraq.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_MAMLUK_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OBELISK">
			<Text>Obelisk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OBELISK_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Egyptian Improvement.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can only be constructed on Antiquity Sites, like a Landmark, but does not remove it. Provides [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_PEACE] Faith, and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OBELISK_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_OBELISK_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An obelisk is a tall, slender, tapered monument with four sides and a pyramidal or pyramidion top. Originally constructed by Ancient Egyptians and called tekhenu, the Greeks used the Greek term obeliskos to describe them, and this word passed into Latin and ultimately English. Ancient obelisks are monolithic and consist of a single stone symbolising the sun god Ra. They played a vital role in religious architecture, being placed in pairs at the entrance of temples.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Around 30 BCE, Rome seized control of Egypt and looted the various temple complexes; in one case they destroyed walls at the Temple of Karnak to haul them out. There are now more than twice as many obelisks that were seized and shipped out by Rome as remain in Egypt. Obelisks were being shipped out of Egypt as late as the nineteenth century when three of them were sent to London, New York and Paris. It is noteworthy that four of the obelisks in the British Museum are actually from Assyria, where they were also erected but as public monuments commemorating the King.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OBELISK">
			<Text>Build an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_OBELISK]Obelisk[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OBELISK_HELP">
			<Text>Does not remove the Antiquity Site.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_OBELISK_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_PEACE] Faith, and [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- England -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WHITE_TOWER">
			<Text>White Tower</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WHITE_TOWER_TEXT">
			<Text>The White Tower is the old keep at the Tower of London. It was built by William the Conqueror during the early 1080s, and was later extended. The White Tower was the castle's strongest defensive point, and originally housed the king and his representatives. Throughout its long history, the Tower has been many things to England: A symbol of tyranny, a treasury, a menagerie, a mint, a palace and a prison. Today, the Tower of London is a vast museum which boasts, amongst its many treasures, the Crown Jewels of the English Monarchy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WHITE_TOWER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WHITE_TOWER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique English replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONWORKS}. In addition to the bonuses of the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONWORKS}, the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WHITE_TOWER} boosts Constabularies, Castles, and Armories; provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for both offensive and defensive Spy actions; and contains a free [ICON_GW_ART] Great Work of Art.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL">
			<Text>Steam Mill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_TEXT">
			<Text>Stationary steam engines are fixed steam engines used for pumping or driving mills and factories, and for power generation. They are distinct from locomotive engines used on railways, traction engines for heavy steam haulage on roads, steam cars (and other motor vehicles), agricultural engines used for ploughing or threshing, marine engines, and the steam turbines used as the mechanism of power generation for most nuclear power plants. They were introduced during the 18th century and widely made for the whole of the 19th century and most of the first half of the 20th century, only declining as electricity supply and the internal combustion engine became more widespread.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEAM_MILL_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_REDCOAT">
			<Text>Redcoat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_REDCOAT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_REDCOAT_TEXT">
			<Text>Despite not being a rare occurence throughout European military history (with Danish, and even French units wearing bright red uniforms at some points), the red uniforms of the infantry of the British Army and Royal Navy have become nationaly and internationaly recognized as unmistakable symbols of the British military power. Originally meant to lower fabrication costs, the diffusion of red uniforms followed a slow process that can be traced back all the way to the War of the Roses in the 15th century. During the reforms that led to the creation of the New Model Army, the red, now considered a staple of English identity, became more prevalent, and stayed that way in the following centuries: its notoriaty came from being worn by British infantry during the whole period of British imperialist policies, from America to Oceania, Africa to Europe and Asia. The only major changes to the color of the uniforms were decided after the lethality of fire became much more prevalent and the red uniform, from a mean of distinction, became a liability. Nonetheless, it kept an important role in British military ceremonial, with royal guards still wearing it during their service.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_REDCOAT_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Ethiopia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STELE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHEWA">
			<Text>Chewa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHEWA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHEWA_TEXT">
			<Text>Chewa were the noble warrior caste of Ethiopian medieval society, appointed by the emperor and furnished with land grants for their service. The Chewa nobility are famous for the use of the Shotel, a dramatically curved double-edged swords that are unique to the Ethiopian Empire. Almost semicircular, the shotel could be used to hook shields, or to reach around them to strike an opponent. The sword could also be used to hook and unhorse a mounted soldier, bringing them to the ground.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CHEWA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OROMO_CAVALRY">
			<Text>Oromo Cavalry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OROMO_CAVALRY_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OROMO_CAVALRY_TEXT">
			<Text>The word "Oromo" refers to the dominant ethnic group in Ethiopia, making up about a third of the total population. The Oromo at times had their own kingdom, language and religion (although in present-day Ethiopia they are evenly split between Muslims and Christians). During the First Italo-Ethiopian War, when Italy attempted to seize Ethiopia as a colonial possession, the Ethiopian emperor Menelik used Oromo cavalrymen to devastating effect, especially in the decisive Battle of Adwa.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Oromo cavalry were not true cavalry, but mounted infantrymen, meaning that they did not fire weapons from horseback, but would gallop towards the Italians, dismount, and then fire. With their lion's-mane headdresses and fierce reputation, they became one of the most feared military units of the era. During the Italian invasion, a rumor spread around the Italian camps that Oromo cavalry (whom the Italians called "Galla" - a word that was seen as offensive by the Oromo) would castrate the bodies of enemies that held weapons - a rumor that caused many Italians to toss aside their guns the moment that the Oromo began their charge. Italian soldiers reported their compatriots turning their guns on themselves rather than facing the Oromo. One report depicts a lone Italian survivor of an Oromo attack, dazed out of his mind, unable to say anything but "Galla cavalry. Galla cavalry. Horror. Horror."</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_OROMO_CAVALRY_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Monolithic Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term "Monolithic Church" (or "rock-hewn church") can be attributed to any church cut from a single stone formation, but is most often used to refer to the complex of 11 churches in Lalibela, Ethiopia. These churches were constructed in the 12th century by King Gebre Mesqel Lalibela, a devout Christian. This 'New Jerusalem' is situated in a mountainous region in the heart of Ethiopia, and is an important center of Christian pilgrimage to this day.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Monolithic Churches are found in places besides Lalibela, including many in Tigray. These churches were almost unknown to the outside world until Abba Tewelde Medhin Josief, a Catholic priest, announced the existence of over 120 rock-hewn churches, 90 of which were still in use. Over the next few years, the total of known churches was raised to 153.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Monolithic Churches can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, and on Hills with no resources and not next to another Monolithic Church.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Can be built on [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, and on Hills with no resources and not next to another Monolithic Church.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Instead of Technologies, Monolithic Churches are improved by completing [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Social Policy Branches[ENDCOLOR] and adopting an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Ideology[ENDCOLOR] or [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Religious Beliefs[ENDCOLOR]:[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] for every Ancient Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for every Medieval Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] for every Industrial Policy Branch,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PEACE] for adopting a Pantheon,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] for founding a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for enhancing a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+1 [ICON_GOLD] and [ICON_PRODUCTION] for reforming a Religion,[NEWLINE]
				+2 [ICON_GOLD] for adopting an Ideology.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH]Monolithic Church[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Monolithic Church, which increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Monolithic Churches increase yields when you adopt more Policies and Beliefs.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- France -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SALON">
			<Text>Salon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SALON_HELP">
			<Text>Possible Theming Bonuses:
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +2 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_ART] Great Works of Art.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +4 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_ART] Great Works of Art from the [COLOR_CYAN]same Era[ENDCOLOR].
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +4 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Foreign[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_ART] Great Works of Art from the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]same Civilization[ENDCOLOR].
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +8 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Foreign[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_ART] Great Works of Art from the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]same Civilization[ENDCOLOR] and the [COLOR_CYAN]same Era[ENDCOLOR].
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SALON_TEXT">
			<Text>A salon is a gathering of people under the roof of an inspiring host, held partly to amuse one another and partly to refine the taste and increase the knowledge of the participants through conversation. These gatherings often consciously followed Horace's definition of the aims of poetry, "either to please or to educate" ("aut delectare aut prodesse est"). Salons, commonly associated with French literary and philosophical movements of the 17th and 18th centuries, were carried on until quite recently in urban settings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SALON_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_SALON_1">
			<Text>Galerie des Batailles</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_SALON_2">
			<Text>Illustrations Architecturales</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_SALON_3">
			<Text>Ensemble de Diplômes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_SALON_4">
			<Text>Collection Exotique</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SALON_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure the Great Work Slots are all filled with Art from the same foreign Civilization and from the same Era.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAD">
			<Text>SPAD S.VII</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAD_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAD_TEXT">
			<Text>World War I saw rapid technological and tactical changes in how wars were fought, including the adoption of aircraft for scouting and bombing. These machines opened an entirely new theatre of war. Despite their promise, the first aircrafts were slow, clumsy, and unreliable due to their underpowered combustion engines. This all changed in 1915 when Marc Birgikt invented a new V8 engine boasting 150 horsepower and weighing only 330 pounds. The French high command saw the new motor's value as an aircraft engine and commissioned a new fighter aircraft: The Société Pour L'Aviation et ses Dérivés, or "SPAD" S. VII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]By late 1916, SPAD VIIs were beginning to see action, and were widely adopted by allied pilots for the rest of the war. Though lacking the maneuverability of older Nieuport fighters, the SPAD VII was unmatched in sheer speed, travelling in excess of 127mph and capable of diving at more than 249mph. Pilots created entirely new tactics to leverage this speed, which gave the SPAD the ability to safely avoid pitched battles. The added stability in diving was especially appreciated over the old Nieuports, which had a bad habit of shedding their wings during maneuvers.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Air superiority became a constant arms race against newer and better German designs and engines. By the end of the war, the SPAD VII's single .303 Vickers machine gun was outmatched by German fighters, which carried at least two machine guns. The heavier and faster SPAD XIII eventually replaced the SPAD VII by late 1917, and saw France through the remainder of the War. Despite its shortcomings, the SPAD series is remembered as one of the fastest and most powerful of WWI fighters.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Germany -->

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWHOUSE">
			<Text>Brewhouse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWHOUSE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWHOUSE_TEXT">
			<Text>Through and through, Germany is a beer culture, whose historic and cultural ties to the drink date back to antiquity. With the professionalization and commodification of brewing in the middle ages, beer moved from a private cottage industry into the inns and public houses, which took the form of Brewhouses (Bräuhauser) and Beer Halls (Bierhaller) in Germany. The greatest and most renowned Brewhouses are found in the Free State of Bavaria, where beer halls, beer gardens, and the annual Oktoberfest have become synonymous with Bavarian culture. Especially notable breweries are found throughout Munich, which are all historically subject to the Bavarian Beer Purity Law -- the Reinheitsegebot -- which dictated that the only ingredients that could be used in the production of beer were water, barley and hops. Adopted by the Bavarian state in 1516, the Reinheitsegebot is one of the oldest pieces of food safety legislation still in effect today. Even before the rise of German nationalism, the Reinheitsegebot had inspired similar regulation in nearby kingdoms and its universal adoption was a condition of Bavaria's unification with Germany in 1871.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As a place where light and food were freely available, the Brewhouses were a cornerstone of public life in southern Germany, acting as the birthplace for numerous revolutionary ideas and movements that gripped Germany in the 18th and 19th centuries. In the wake of the French Revolution, German liberals organized in the Beer Halls of Munich to demand reforms of the monarchy in a series of uprisings from 1848 to 1849. During the 1910s, Vladimir Lenin was a frequent patron of the Munich Hofbräuhaus, where he did much of his political agitations and initial founding of the Bolshevik party, which would go on to form the Soviet Union. Most famous, however, was Adolf Hitler, who announced the formation of his National Socialist (Nazi) Party at the Hofbräuhaus am Platzl in 1920, and was arrested for treason in 1923 after a failed coup d'état at the Bürgerbräukeller. This episode became known as the Beer Hall Putsch, and the resulting trial gave Hitler a national platform to spread his political ideology, leading to his widespread fame and the rise of German fascism.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWHOUSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KRUPP_GUN">
			<Text>Krupp Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KRUPP_GUN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KRUPP_GUN_TEXT">
			<Text>A Krupp Gun is any member of a family of artillery pieces created by the Krupp family commercial steelworks, based in Essen. The Krupp Guns were the first cast steel field guns to enter mass production and adoption by any military, with the Royal Prussian Army's first purchase in 1856. Krupp Guns were renowned for their quality and for being at the forefront of new developments in artillery.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]At the outbreak of World War I, the German army doctrine emphasized mobility and the use of howitzer guns which fired in higher arcs to hit entrenched enemies at steeper angles. This doctrine paid early dividends during the initial stages of the Schlieffen Plan, where smaller, lighter German guns worked well as they marched through Belgium and Northern France, and raced the British to the sea. Though the bulk of their artillery was smaller pieces, like the 7.7 cm FK 96, the Germans also had some of the most impressive heavy artillery of the war with the Minenwerfers, or "mine throwers", short range artillery that outperformed contemporary mortars at a fraction of the weight. As the war began, Germany deployed twelve experimental 45 cm minenwerfer siege guns, some of the largest field artillery pieces ever produced. Affectionately dubbed "Big Bertha" by the German troops, these siege guns punched through dozens of hardened fortresses around Liege and Mauberge, taking the German army within striking distance of Paris in a matter of weeks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KRUPP_GUN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Greece -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GYMNASION">
			<Text>Gymnasion</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GYMNASION_HELP">
			<Text>Possible Theming Bonuses:
  			[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +4 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_WRITING] Great Works of Writing.
  			[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +6 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Foreign[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_WRITING] Great Works of Writing.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GYMNASION_TEXT">
			<Text>The Gymnasion were training facilities used by adult Greek men to socialize and practice for public games. The name roughly translates to "naked training place", because all athletes practiced while naked, and usually while covered in olive oil. Gymnasia started as open fields outside city limits, but were later planned as enclosed spaces that were central to Greek public life. While the public games and festivals were important themselves, Gymnasia also became centers of arts and learning. The famous schools of philosophy in Athens - the Academic school founded by Plato, the Peripatetic School founded by Aristotle, and the Cynic school founded by Antisthenes - were all founded and named after the Gymnasia where they met.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GYMNASION_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KLEPHT">
			<Text>Klepht</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KLEPHT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KLEPHT_TEXT">
			<Text>Bandits and mountainfolk, turned anti-Ottoman insurgents and freedom fighters, The Klephts were the bedrock upon which the modern Greek army was formed. Together with the men originally hired to capture them, the Armatoloi, the Klephts formed the "yeast of liberty", the first hope for Greek independence after more than four centuries of Ottoman rule.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Undisciplined and flighty as one would expect of brigands, Klephts waged an effective guerilla campaign against the much larger Ottoman armies sent to subdue them.  Massacres on both sides of the conflict were inflicted, but European sympathies fell heavily in favor of the Greeks. The unbridled cruelty of the Muslim Ottomans outraged Europe's citizenry, who raised supplies, food and volunteers to fight for a Hellenic independence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After 8 years, Ottoman forces had finally managed to crush the revolt, but where Greek soldiers had failed poets and propaganda had succeeded. French, British, and Russian governments each sent a fleet in defense of the Greek islands in response to popular demand for intervention. In the face of such overwhelming force, the Ottomans sued for peace and liberated Greece. After more than 2,000 years under the boots of Macedonian, Roman and Ottoman conquerors, The Greek homeland was at last free -- unified as one people for the first time in history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_KLEPHT_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Huns -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EKI">
			<Text>Eki</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EKI_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EKI_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]'Eki' is a term that the Huns likely used to describe the earth, particularly that which was essential to grazing livestock. Nomadic pastoralism is a form of pastoralism where livestock are herded in order to find fresh grazing land. Strictly speaking, true nomads follow an irregular pattern of movement, in contrast with transhumance where seasonal pastures are fixed. However this distinction is often not observed and the term nomad used for both - in historical cases the regularity of movements is often unknown in any case. The herded livestock include cattle, yaks, sheep, goats, reindeer, horses, donkeys or camels, or mixtures of species. Nomadic pastoralism is commonly practiced in regions with little arable land, typically in the developing world. Of the estimated 30 to 40 million nomadic pastoralists worldwide, most are found in central Asia and the Sahel region of West Africa. Increasing numbers of stock may lead to overgrazing of the area and desertification if lands are not allowed to fully recover between one grazing period and the next. Increased enclosure and fencing of land has reduced the amount of land available for this practice.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EKI_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built on flat land tiles without access to Fresh Water. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent to two[ENDCOLOR] other Eki. Can be built [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in or adjacent to[ENDCOLOR] Hunnic territory. When completed, claims the tile beneath it if built in [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Neutral Territory[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_EKI]Eki[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 Ekis adjacent to this Eki. Can only be built on flat land tiles without access to Fresh Water. Can be built [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]in or adjacent to[ENDCOLOR] Hunnic territory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building it in neutral territory instantly claims the tile for the Hunnic Empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EKI_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]adjacent to two[ENDCOLOR] other Ekis.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TARKHAN">
			<Text>Tarkhan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TARKHAN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TARKHAN_TEXT">
			<Text>Tarkhan were nobles and high-ranking commanders within the armies of the Xiongnu and Hunnic empires. The term spread throughout the languages and peoples of the steppes, appearing as a title within Turkic, Mongol and Iranian cultures, even becoming a common boys name. Analogous to modern day commanders, the Tarkhan were the protectors and conquerors of the Hunnic empire, spurring their civilization forward to greatness.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TARKHAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ULTICUR">
			<Text>Ulticur</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ULTICUR_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ULTICUR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Huns' origins remain shrouded in mystery, but one clue to their Xiongnu heritage is their rule by an Ulticur, or "Six-Horns Council". The Ulticur was a small council of nobles, the most powerful men within the Hunnic Empire besides the emperor himself. Each was seated according to their standing with the emperor, with the emperor's favorite seated to his immediate right.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An emperor's legitimacy depended heavily on the tributes he could extract from the surrounding kingdoms and distribute to his nobles. It is surmised that insufficient tributes from the Chinese and other client tribes triggered the decline and disappearance of the Xiongnu in East Asia, only for them reappear as the Huns of Eastern Europe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ULTICUR_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Inca -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_WARAKAQ">
			<Text>Warak'aq</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_WARAKAQ_TEXT">
			<Text>The Inca warriors were renowned slingers. Their projectile of choice was a rounded stone. While a sling does not have the range or stopping power of a bow and arrow, slings are remarkably small and light weapons, and infantry warriors could easily carry them without becoming encumbered. And as is written in the Old Testament, a trained slinger can kill even the largest opponent with but a single stone...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_WARAKAQ_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The {TXT_KEY_UNIT_WARAKAQ} is the Incan unique unit, replacing the {TXT_KEY_UNIT_INCAN_SLINGER}. It has superior range and can daze enemy units which lowers their [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength for a long time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Use it to harass your foes and take down Barbarian camps quickly.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_WARAKAQ_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TERRACE_FARM_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every {TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERRACE_FARM} or Mountain adjacent to this {TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERRACE_FARM}. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to adjacent Farms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TERRACE_FARM_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food if adjacent to mountains or other Pata-pata. Provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food to adjacent Farms.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLQA">
			<Text>Qullqa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLQA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLQA_TEXT">
			<Text>Qullqa were storage silos located along roadsides near cities and political centers across the Tawantinsuyu. The vast network of Qullqas stored food and supplies for the general populace and the military. This system acted as emergency reserves for the peasantry to protect against the frequent crop failures that took place in the precarious, high-altitude communities throughout the Inca's domains. The storehouses also relieved soldiers from the need to forage, but required constant maintenance from the local populace.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Maintaining and stocking the Qullqa system was the responsibility of local lords who resided in stations called Tambos, each located within a day's march of the next. Royal Qullqa stored the luxury and ceremonial goods of the Incan nobility, including feathers, precious stones, and Coca leaves. Coca production was jealously guarded as an imperial monopoly; cultivation and distribution of coca was strictly under the control of the nobles and a few favored classes. In fact, the entire economy of the Incan Empire functioned off a command economy, where access to and control of the goods stored in the Qullqa system ensured the wellbeing and continued expansion of the empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QULLQA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INTI_MACEMAN">
			<Text>Inti Maceman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INTI_MACEMAN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INTI_MACEMAN_TEXT">
			<Text>The standing army of the Inca was formed primarily by nobles, but the Sapa Inca could raise an army of able-bodied men from the general populace at will. Military discipline was strictly enforced when the troops were on the march and the army, although variously specialized, was extremely well trained. Drawing on the resources of a vast empire, the Inca recruited warriors from numerous subordinate tribes with their own military traditions. The Chimu, inheritors of the ancient Moche culture were once bitter enemies of the Inca but, once subdued, provided the Inca with some of their most formidable and loyal troops. The Chimu were known for their use of maces and clubs in warfare. Some warriors strode fearlessly into battle, carrying massive maces that required both hands to swing and decimated anything in their path. These elite shock troops posed a deadly threat to any opponent, whether in the field or in a fortification under siege.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INTI_MACEMAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- India -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARAPPAN_RESERVOIR">
			<Text>Harappan Reservoir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARAPPAN_RESERVOIR_TEXT">
			<Text>The ancient Harappan and Indus Valley Civilizations of Northwest South Asia, including Pakistan and parts of India, were prominent in hydraulic engineering, and had many water supply and sanitation devices that were the first of their kind. Among other things, they contained the world's earliest known system of flush toilets. These existed in many homes, and were connected to a common sewerage pipe. Most houses also had private wells. City walls functioned as a barrier against floods, and massive reservoirs were often constructed along these walls to collect this floodwater to save for droughts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARAPPAN_RESERVOIR_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARAPPAN_RESERVOIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Indian replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUEDUCT}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUEDUCT}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARAPPAN_RESERVOIR} keeps more [ICON_FOOD] Food on [ICON_CITIZEN] population growth; boosts Farms; and increases the city's [ICON_FOOD] Food generation depending on the number of followers of this city's majority [ICON_RELIGION] religion.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DHANURDHARA">
			<Text>Dhanurdhara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DHANURDHARA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DHANURDHARA_TEXT">
			<Text>Archery was the most highly revered martial art of ancient India. Many of the culture heroes and gods of the Vedic texts describe archers of unparalleled skill, including Arjuna, Rama, Karna, and even Shiva himself. Traditional Indian bows are described as long, matching the height of their users, but without the tremendous strength of the Welsh longbow.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DHANURDHARA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Indonesia -->

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DJONG">
			<Text>Djong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DJONG_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DJONG_TEXT">
			<Text>At the time of their creation in the 1st century CE, the Djong were easily the largest, most capable seagoing vessels anywhere in the world. Averaging at over 400 tons of cargo and capable of withstanding the typhoon winds, these marvels of engineering extended the Javanese trade networks from northern China to Ghana. At the time of the Majapahit Empire, Djong were armed with the earliest breech-loading cannons, the brass cetbang, which helping them conquer the entire Indonsesian Archipelago. Djong were still widely used until the 16th century, and the methods for designing Djong ships spread throughout Asia, influencing the creation of China's iconic junk boats.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_DJONG_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Kampong</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KAMPONG_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KAMPONG_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term 'Sama-Bajau' refers to a single ethnic group scattered between the modern day Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The Sama people live a semi-sedentary life in stilt villages or "kampongs" in coastal shallows, while Bajau refers to nomadic groups living in house boats. The Sama-Bajau defy national and ethnic borders, travelling and fishing between islands on the open ocean. The Sama-Bajau were frequently employed as privateers and raiders by the Srivijayan kingdoms. Bajau-Laut possess unique abilities which allow them to see better underwater, and dive longer and deeper than any other group of humans.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In recent years, the Bajau-Laut have been forced into sedentary lifestyles by various governments, and face discrimination as pagans, outsiders and squatters. A combination of overfishing and modernization threatens the Bajau's nomadic traditions, as they have been forcibly resettled on land. Still, a few communities of Bajau-Laut ride their lepa lepa across the blue water of Southeast Asia, only traveling to shore a few times each year.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Indonesian Improvement. The Kampong can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Embarked Workers on Coastal and Lake Tiles, and not next to another Kampong.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Kampong yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KAMPONG">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_INDONESIA_KAMPONG]Kampong[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KAMPONG_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Kampong, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KAMPONG_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Iroquois -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PROWLER">
			<Text>Prowler</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PROWLER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PROWLER_TEXT">
			<Text>Unlike many other tribes, the Iroquois had easy access to trade goods at Dutch forts along the Hudson River, and traded for various goods and luxuries. Weapons of war such as the iron axe and musket were highly sought after, and by the 1640s the Iroquois were well-equipped to fight their traditional Huron and Algonquian enemies. Common muskets were given in exchange for pelts and food, but often of lighter and smaller caliber than military-grade muskets. The Dutch and British feared giving high-quality weapons to people who could turn against them, but the Iroquois often found the smaller weapons more suitable to rough terrain anyways.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]War tactics were changed after the Iroquois' acquisition of firearms. The lethality of their new weapons put the Iroquois, never a highly populous group, in a precarious position. The tribes' custom of absorbing refugees and prisoners of war changed as fewer and fewer warriors survived clashes with European arms. Great armies walking with prominent chiefs and shamans were replaced with guerilla tactics, small bands of troops guided by commanders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PROWLER_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TADODAHO">
			<Text>Tadodaho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TADODAHO_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TADODAHO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Tadodaho, also called the Fire Keeper, refers to the head of the Grand Council of the Six Nations that includes the Cayuga, Mohawk, Oneida, Onondaga, Seneca, and Tuscarora people. A spiritual and political leader, the position dates back to the original founding of the Iroquois Confederacy; the hoyenah (chieftain) of the Onondaga Nation in the time of Hiawatha and the Great Peacemaker was named Tadodaho. The leadership of the Grand Council, and the honorific title of its founder, has been passed down for centuries, and is a lifetime appointment. It is said there have been 27 Tadodahos since the original founding of the Haudenosaunee (also called Iroquois) Confederacy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Great Council Fire of the Iroquois League is still located within the Onondaga reservation in present-day New York. The Tadodahos of recent history have continued to fight for the repatriation and preservation of Haudenosaunee culture, language, and history, as well as petition the American and Canadian governments in defense of their people's lands and treaty rights.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_TADODAHO_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Japan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOJO">
			<Text>Dojo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOJO_TEXT">
			<Text>A dojo is a Japanese term which literally means "place of the way". Initially, dojos were adjunct to temples. The term can refer to a formal training place for any of the Japanese do arts but typically it is considered the formal gathering place for students of any Japanese martial arts style such as karate, judo, or samurai, to conduct training, examinations and other related encounters. The concept of a dojo only referring to a training place specifically for Asian martial arts is a Western concept; in Japan, any physical training facility, including professional wrestling schools, may be called dojo because of its close martial arts roots.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOJO_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOJO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Japanese replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMORY}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMORY}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOJO} provides more training experience and more military supply; grants the {TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_BUSHIDO} promotion to all melee, gunpowder, mounted and armored units, which offers one of eight possible promotions to these unit types after their first combat and increases the unit's strength as it takes damage; and produces [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when units gain experience in combat.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KABUKI_THEATER">
			<Text>Kabuki Theater</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KABUKI_THEATER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KABUKI_THEATER_TEXT">
			<Text>Kabuki is a classical Japanese dance-drama known for the stylization of its drama and for the elaborate make-up worn by some of its performers. The art form was created in 1603 when Izumo no Okuni, a miko of Izumo-taisha, began performing a new style of dance drama in the dry riverbeds of Kyoto. Despite many the upheaval of Japans modernization, Kabuki remains the most popular of the traditional styles of Japanese drama, and has helped renew interest in other forms of traditional Japanese art.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KABUKI_THEATER_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YAMATO">
			<Text>Yamato</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YAMATO_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YAMATO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Yamato-class battleships were the crown jewel of the Imperial Japanese Navy during World War II. Displacing 73,000 tonnes at full load, they were the heaviest and most powerfully armed battleships ever constructed. Each Yamato carried nine 18.1 inch guns, the largest naval artillery ever fitted to a warship, each capable of firing 3,000 lb. shells over 26 miles. Two battleships of the class, Yamato and Musashi, were completed while a third, Shinano, was converted to an aircraft carrier during construction. All were sunk by American forces during WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Due to their size, speed, and power, The Yamato-class visibly embodied Japan's determination and readiness to defend its interests against the western powers, especially the United States. One of the reasons that the warship may have such significance in Japanese culture is that the word "Yamato" was often used as a poetic name for Japan itself. Thus, the construction and destruction of the Yamato battleships became symbolic for the rise and fall of Japanese imperial aspirations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YAMATO_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Korea -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEOWON">
			<Text>Seowon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEOWON_TEXT">
			<Text>Seowon were the most common educational institution of Korea during the mid- to late-Joseon Dynasty. They were private institutions combining the functions of a Confucian shrine and a preparatory school. In educational terms, the seowon were primarily occupied with preparing students for the national civil service examinations. In most cases, seowon served only pupils of the aristocratic yangban class.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEOWON_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEOWON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Korean replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEOWON} boosts [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works and Great Person Tile Improvements, and provides a bigger [ICON_RESEARCH] Science boost on [ICON_CITIZEN] population growth.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAEBOL">
			<Text>Chaebol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAEBOL_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAEBOL_TEXT">
			<Text>Chaebol are powerful multi-national corporations originating in South Korea. Beginning as family businesses, generous government investment allowed the Chaebols to quickly industrialize South Korea's agricultural society, in what was called the Miracle on the Han River. The Chaebol became central to the South Korean economy and came to represent the invincibility of South Korea's industrial might until the financial crashes the late 20th century, which saw several important Chaebol declare bankruptcy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Chaebol continue to dominate the South Korean economy and social fabric, and some like Samsung and Hyundai have become household names worldwide. Today, Chaebol account for over 80% of South Korea's exports, and the largest single Chaebol accounts for 17% of the entire nation's GDP.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHAEBOL_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Maya -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KUNA">
			<Text>Kuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KUNA_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KUNA_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]'Kuna' is the Mayan word for temple or church. Mayan Kuna were similar in design to the ziggurats and pyramids of Eurasia. Though the Kuna themselves are largely all that remain of these ancient sites, they were once the focal points of large cities. Most famous of these is Chichen Itza, a sight so grand that it qualifies as a World Wonder!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KUNA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Mayan Improvement.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can only be constructed in Forests or Jungles, and cannot be adjacent to another Kuna.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_KUNA]Kuna[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built adjacent to another Kuna.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KUNA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PITZ_COURT">
			<Text>Pitz Court</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PITZ_COURT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PITZ_COURT_TEXT">
			<Text>The Mesoamerican Ball Game, or 'Pitz', is a game of ritual and cultural significance among the Mayan people. The object of the game is to keep the ball in play for as long as possible by striking back and forth within a sloped arena using the hips, though some variations allowed for elbows, shoulders and even rackets. The earliest archaeological evidence of the game come from a court estimated to be 3400 years old.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Over 1300 different ballcourts have been found within Mayan ruins, with relatively little variation in size or layout over thousands of years. Every court is shaped as a narrow alley with gently sloping walls on either side and enclosed endzones. This gave the court a roughly H-shaped layout. Later versions of the ballcourts would include hoops at the midpoint, suspended on the walls. Actually sending a ball through the ring must have been a rare occurrence, since the players could not use their hands or feet to guide the ball. Moreover, the rings were only slightly larger than the ball itself and were a long way from the playing alley.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The game was more than a mere sporting event to the Mayan people, serving as a substitute for war in the case of a dispute between cities. Later Classical Mayan art suggests a link between the ball game and ritual sacrifice, with winners being decapitated as an offering to the gods. The Maya Twin Myth of the Popol Vuh describes the game between the Hero Twins, Hunahpu and Xbalanque, and lords of the underworld, One Death and Seven Death. The game was played so the Hero Twins might recover Hunahpu's head, which was being used as a ball by the Lords (Hunahpu had been using a squash for his head until his real one could be recovered).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PITZ_COURT_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HOLKAN">
			<Text>Holkan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HOLKAN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HOLKAN_TEXT">
			<Text>The Maya are often idealized as a peaceful civilization by western historians, but the Maya were not strangers to war. Unlike the wars of Europe and Asia, however, the Maya engaged in a highly ritualized form of combat based on astrological and religious concerns as much as political ones. Squabbles over land, influence, and resources were common, but the need for human sacrifices was also a factor leading to war.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The nobility and priesthood of Mayan cities kept a monopoly on violence, making all but the most desperate of wars strictly within the affairs of the upper class. Weapons made of obsidian and chert were stockpiled within the palaces of lords and kings, who would call upon their family to lead raids. The leaders of such expeditions were known as 'Holkan'.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HOLKAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Mongolia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GER">
			<Text>Ger</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GER_TEXT">
			<Text>A yurt, called a 'Ger' by Mongolians, is a portable, bent dwelling structure traditionally used by nomads in the steppes of Central Asia as their home. The structure comprises a crown or compression wheel, usually steam bent, supported by roof ribs which are bent down at the end where they meet the lattice wall (again, steam bent). The top of the wall is prevented from spreading by means of a tension band which opposes the force of the roof ribs. The structure is usually covered by layers of fabric and sheep's wool felt for insulation and weatherproofing. The traditional decoration within a yurt is primarily pattern based. These patterns are generally not according to taste, but are derived from sacred ornaments with certain symbolism. Symbols representing strength are among the most common, including the khas (swastika) and four powerful beasts (lion, tiger, garuda and dragon), as well as stylized representations of the five elements (fire, water, earth, metal, and wood), considered to be the fundamental, unchanging elements of the cosmos. Such patterns are commonly used in the home with the belief that they will bring strength and offer protection.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GER_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMOKEHOUSE}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMOKEHOUSE}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GER} generates [ICON_PEACE] Faith; boosts pastures; provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when borders expand; and makes borders expand faster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ORDO">
			<Text>Ordo</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ORDO_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ORDO_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Simply translated, "ordo" means "palace tent." However, an ordo was something much more than just a simple tent - it was the center of the tribe for the nomadic Mongolians.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An ordo served as the headquarters and main encampment for the Khan and his warriors. Though built for travel, it had style, from simple decorations to carefully sewn patterns. The ordo moved with the Khan and his warriors as they went on campaign, ensuring they always felt at home no matter where they traveled.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You can construct an Ordo anywhere within your territory, or directly adjacent to your territory. Upon constructing the Ordo, your Military Unit Supply Cap will increase by 1, and your Cultural borders will also expand to surround the Ordo on all sides by one hex. If the new Cultural border claims hexes already owned by another civilization, you will incur a diplomatic penalty as a result. Unlike the Citadel, any enemy unit which ends its turn next to an Ordo takes no damage.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ORDO_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Mongolian Great Person Tile Improvement, replacing the {TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CITADEL}. Can only be constructed by a {TXT_KEY_UNIT_MONGOL_KHAN}.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building an Ordo claims adjacent tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile. Units moving onto an Ordo have all their [ICON_MOVES] Movement restored. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ORDO">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ORDO]Ordo[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ORDO_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built in owned territory or adjacent to your own borders in an unowned tile, and cannot be adjacent to other Ordos. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Constructing the Ordo will expand your Cultural borders to surround the Ordo, increase your [ICON_WAR] Military Unit Supply Cap by 1, and will consume this unit. If the new Cultural border claims hexes already owned by another civilization, you will incur a diplomatic penalty as a result.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile. Restores [ICON_MOVES] Movement for any Unit moving onto this tile. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BLACK_TUG">
			<Text>Black Tug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BLACK_TUG_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BLACK_TUG_TEXT">
			<Text>A tug is a pole with circularly arranged horse tail-hairs of varying colors arranged at the top -- a symbol of the importance of horses in Mongol life. A white-haired banner is used as a peacetime symbol, while the black banner was for wartime. The original white banner disappeared early in history, but the black banner survived as the repository of Genghis Khan's soul. The Mongols continued to honor the banner, building a monastery to guard it, but the tug was eventually lost amidst the Stalinist purges of Mongolian nationalists, monks, and intellectuals in 1937.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Nine White banners of Mongolia were revived after democracy was adopted in the early 1990s, replacing the previous communist flags. The modern Mongolian nine white banners are kept in the Government Palace in Ulaanbaatar; the modern Mongolian black banners are kept in the Ministry of Defense.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_BLACK_TUG_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROJECT_YASSA">
			<Text>Adopt the Yassa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROJECT_YASSA_HELP">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_PRODUCTION_BUILDING_GLOBAL_EFFECTS}[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for [COLOR_YELLOW]{TXT_KEY_UNITCOMBAT_ARCHER} Units[ENDCOLOR] in all Cities[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for [COLOR_YELLOW]{TXT_KEY_UNITCOMBAT_SIEGE} Units[ENDCOLOR] in all Cities[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for [COLOR_YELLOW]{TXT_KEY_UNITCOMBAT_MOUNTED} Units[ENDCOLOR] in all Cities[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+20% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for [COLOR_YELLOW]{TXT_KEY_UNITCOMBAT_ARMOR} Units[ENDCOLOR] in all Cities[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]-40% [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Empire Size Modifier from number of Cities in all Cities[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]When conquering a City: +10 [ICON_GOLD] +10 [ICON_RESEARCH] +10 [ICON_CULTURE] in all Cities, scaling with Era[NEWLINE]----------------[NEWLINE]Prerequisite Technology: [COLOR_CYAN]{TXT_KEY_TECH_PHILOSOPHY_TITLE}[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]Max 1 per Player</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROJECT_YASSA_TEXT">
			<Text>Yassa was a secret written code of law created by Genghis Khan. The word Yassa translates into "order" or "decree". It was the de facto law of the Mongol Empire even though the "law" was never actually made public. The Yassa seems to have originated from decrees issued in wartime, and was later codified and expanded to include cultural and life-style conventions. By keeping the Yassa secret, the decrees could be modified and used selectively. It is believed that the Yassa was supervised by Genghis Khan himself with the help of the high judge of the Mongol Empire: His stepbrother, Shihihutag. Genghis Khan appointed his second son Chagatai (a.k.a. Chagatai Khan) to oversee the execution of the laws.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROJECT_YASSA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Morocoo -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIAD">
			<Text>Riad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIAD_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIAD_TEXT">
			<Text>A Riad is a traditional North African house built in a peristyle format, surrounding an interior garden or courtyard. These homes were often plain on the exterior, but lavishly decorated inside, projecting humility and austerity while preserving a family's comfort and privacy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]While architectural style has changed over the years, the riad's basic form is still used in modern design. Riads enjoyed something of a renaissance during French occupation of North Africa. As befitting Europe's fascination with preserving historic heritage sites, restoration efforts on old Riads were undertaken throughout Morocco's major cities, often converting old Riads into hotels or restaurants.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIAD_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CORSAIR">
			<Text>Corsair</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CORSAIR_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CORSAIR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Barbary Corsairs were Muslim pirates and privateers operating off the coast of North Africa who became infamous throughout Europe. Ranging throughout the Mediterranean and as far as Iceland, the Corsairs slaughtered livestock and captured Christians for sale in the slave markets of the Islamic world. The frequency and ferocity of these raids, or "Razzia" was such that long stretches of Italian and Spanish coast were abandoned for fear of abduction. It is estimated that some 1.25 million people were enslaved by Barbary corsairs between 1530 and 1780 A.D.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The scope of Corsair activity began to diminish in the latter part of the 17th century, as the more powerful European navies started to pose a real threat to the Barbary States. However, Christian shipping and coastlines continued to suffer until the early 19th century. Following the Napoleonic Wars and the Congress of Vienna in 1814, European powers agreed upon the need to suppress the Barbary Corsairs for good. The razzias finally ceased after the Second Barbary War between the Barbary pirates and the United States, the impetus for the creation of the US Navy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"It is written in our Koran, that all nations which do not acknowledge the Prophet are sinners, whom it is the right and duty of the faithful to plunder and enslave; and that every mu'min (believer) who is slain in this warfare is sure to go to paradise."[NEWLINE][TAB]- Sidi Haji Abdrahaman, to Thomas Jefferson in reply to his demand for the protection of American merchant ships</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CORSAIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Netherlands -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built on Marsh tiles or on featureless Lake/Coast tiles adjacent to at least 3 land tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_WATER_HELP">
			<Text>Allows land units to traverse this tile without embarkation. Can only be built on Marsh tiles or on featureless Lake/Coast tiles adjacent to at least 3 land tiles.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_POLDER_WATER_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Allows land units to traverse this tile without embarkation.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOELEN">
			<Text>Doelen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOELEN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOELEN_TEXT">
			<Text>Within the cities of the Low Countries, the institution of policing has its roots in the schutterij, a voluntary town watch and citizen militia. Membership in the town's schuttersgilde was often undertaken by wealthy burghers as a stepping stone for further public posts in the city. The Schutterij were responsible for military support during a siege or revolt, fire, and for closing and re-opening the city gates each day. Because of their secondary function as social clubs for wealthy and ambitious young men, the schutterij held undue influence over municipal politics, and often took upon themselves additional responsibilities such as hosting public banquets, religious functions, and philanthropic work. The officers regularly paid for group portraits of the members, some of which are still highly regarded as the finest paintings produced by the Dutch Golden Age.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The training grounds for schutters were called Doelen, meaning "target range". Doelen typically were placed near the city walls and consisted of an outdoor firing range with an adjoining hall for gymnastic exercise and meetings. Many Doelen throughout the Netherlands have been preserved, though often converted into school gymnasiums, libraries, or community halls.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOELEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GOEDENDAG">
			<Text>Goedendag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GOEDENDAG_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GOEDENDAG_TEXT">
			<Text>A Goedendag is a four-foot long club with a spearhead at its tip that was used by the militias of Medieval Flanders during the Franco-Flemish War. The weapon was christened "goedendag" by the French, a cognate with the Dutch greeting "good day". This name may be a reference to the Bruges Matins massacre of 1302, in which the guildsmen of Bruges took over the city by greeting people in the streets and murdering anyone who answered with a French accent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Goedendags were used to great effect by the guildsmen of Flanders against the French knights, but exactly how the weapon was used is a source of debate. Contemporary illustrations show it being used as a club, written accounts describe its first use as a spear to meet a charge, then a club as the enemy was halted. However they worked, men armed with Goedendags marked the beginning of the end for heavy cavalry in Western Europe, and the dawn of an "Infantry Revolution" where peasant militia were now a credible threat to professional soldiers. The stunning victory of common men over foreign tyrants became a wellspring of romantic nationalism for the Low Countries.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"each held his godendart (sic) raised against the French, the iron as one meets a wild boar"[NEWLINE][TAB]- Guillaume Guiart, a contemporary account describing the battle of Courtrai, 1302 A.D.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GOEDENDAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Ottoman -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIEGE_FOUNDRY">
			<Text>Siege Foundry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIEGE_FOUNDRY_TEXT">
			<Text>A foundry is a factory that produces metal castings. Metals are cast into shapes by melting them into a liquid, pouring the metal in a mold, and removing the mold material or casting after the metal has solidified as it cools. The most common metals processed are aluminium and cast iron. However, other metals, such as bronze, brass, steel, magnesium, and zinc, are also used to produce castings in foundries. In this process, parts of desired shapes and sizes can be formed. In the context of war, foundries were essential to the production of cannonry and other essential siege equipment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIEGE_FOUNDRY_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIEGE_FOUNDRY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Ottoman replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORGE}. In addition to the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORGE}'s bonuses, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SIEGE_FOUNDRY} generates [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from producing military units, produces Siege units more quickly, and grants them the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]{TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_VOLLEY}[ENDCOLOR] Promotion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Use these abilities to build a massive force of artillery to take down enemies' walls and conquer their lands!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD">
			<Text>Great Bombard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_TEXT">
			<Text>Bigger is better, and biggest is best. The super-sized bombards of the late medieval were first used in Western European warfare at the beginning of the 15th century, but it was the Ottomans that would realize the bombard's full potential at the Siege of Constantinople in 1453. Unable to find patronage with the Byzantine emperor, a Hungarian gunfounder named Orban sold his services to Mehmed II of the Ottoman Empire, and began crafting bronze cannons capable of lobbing 1.6 tons of shaped stone more than a mile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Transporting such massive weapons took as many as 60 oxen, and required construction of entire road networks before the cannons could be brought to bear against the impregnable Theodosian Walls. Within a day of the opening bombardment, massive stones smashed the outer defenses to rubble and the city which had stood as a fortress of Christendom for a millennium fell. The sack of Constantinople raged for three days following, and triggered a mass exodus of Greeks into Europe proper. The influx of Byzantine refugees brought a rediscovery of the philosophical and intellectual achievements of Greek culture into Western Europe, planting the seeds of the Renaissance.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Stone bombards were supplanted by iron-ball cannons by the end of the 16th century, and few bombards are left intact. None of the bombard's descendants, however, can claim to have single-handedly ended an era.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_1">
			<Text>Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_2">
			<Text>Dardanelles Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_3">
			<Text>Mohammed's Great Gun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_4">
			<Text>Orban's Cannon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_BOMBARD_5">
			<Text>Kalle Acici</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERSANE">
			<Text>Tersane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Ottoman Great Person Tile Improvement. Can be built by Expending a [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral or embarked [ICON_GREAT_GENERAL] Great General adjacent to a City and not adjacent to another Tersane.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. +25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 Experience for Naval Units built in the City owning this tile. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building a Tersane claims adjacent tiles. Units standing on a Tersane receive +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERSANE_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_TERSANE_HELP}The Turkish word 'Tersane' is derived from the Venetian 'darsane', from which the English word 'arsenal' is also derived. Though never at the forefront of shipbuilding technology, the Ottomans enjoyed over a century of naval dominance in the Mediterranean following their conquest of Constantinople in 1453. The largest Tersane, constructed at the Golden Horn across from Constantinople, housed over 160 docks, drydocks, storehouses and supply depots, making it one of the largest centers of commerce and industry in the Mediterranean.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ottoman naval power was maintained through its tremendous shipbuilding capacity and its allegiances to the Barbary corsairs of North Africa. This pre-eminence was finally ended at the battle of Lepanto, where a combined Spanish and Venetian armada delivered a crushing defeat to the Ottomans, capturing or destroying more than two thirds of the Ottoman navy. In response, the Ottomans built 250 new vessels within six months.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"You come to see how we bear our misfortune. But I would have you know the difference between your loss and ours. In wresting Cyprus from you, we deprived you of an arm; in defeating our fleet, you have only shaved our beard."[NEWLINE][TAB] - Grand Vizier Mehmed Sokullu, on the defeat at Lepanto, and the capture of Cyprus, which the Ottomans had taken earlier the same year
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TERSANE">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_OTTOMAN_TERSANE]Tersane[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TERSANE_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built in water next to an owned City, and cannot be adjacent to another Tersane.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building the Tersane will expand your Cultural borders to surround the Tersane, increase your [ICON_WAR] Military Unit Supply Cap by 1, and will consume this Unit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 Experience for Naval Units built in the City owning this tile. Units standing on a Tersane receive +50% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Persia -->

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CHARBAGH">
			<Text>Charbagh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CHARBAGH_TEXT">
			<Text>A Charbagh is a walled garden divided into four square sections that is distinctive to Indo-Persian culture. These gardens trace their roots to the pairidaeza of the Achaemenid empire, and perhaps back even further to Assyrian garden designs. Charbagh construction was an invaluable a tool of state, demonstrating a king's ability to bring life to an otherwise desolate area; the angular, ordered construction served as a contrast the chaos of nature. Persian and later Persianized cultures employed garden building as a subtle way to demonstrate the King of King's command over his realm and the natural world within it through the creation of public spaces.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Persian gardens have captured the imaginations of Mediterranean and western thinkers. The pairidaeza is the root of the Greek "paradise", informing modern notions of an earthly Eden in art and poetry.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Charbagh can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Workers on Land with access to Fresh Water, and not next to another Charbagh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Charbagh yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. During a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, the Charbagh's yields are increased by +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, in addition to the usual +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in City for each worked Charbagh.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CHARBAGH_HELP">
			<Text>The Charbagh can be built by [ICON_WORKER] Workers on Land with access to Fresh Water, and not next to another Charbagh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each Charbagh yields [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. During a [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age, the Charbagh's yields are increased by +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, in addition to the usual +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People Points in City for each worked Charbagh.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHARBAGH">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_PERSIA_CHARBAGH]Charbagh[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHARBAGH_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Charbagh, which increases [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and increases the rate of [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHARBAGH_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation rate.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_QIZILBASH">
			<Text>Qizilbash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_QIZILBASH_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_QIZILBASH_TEXT">
			<Text>Qizilbash (Tr: "red-heads") was originally a pejorative for the followers of the Safawiyyah Sufi order. Named for their distinctive crimson headwear, the Qizilbash organized into a Shi'ite society reminiscent of a European knightly order. Though primarily of Turkman origin, the Qizilbash proved instrumental in the establishment of the Iranian Safavid Dynasty.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In a campaign to avenge the death of his father, Ismail I led 7000 Qizilbash warriors to victory over an Aq Qoyunlu force of 30 000, and established the Safavid State. Within eleven short years, Ismail brought all of Iran under his control, becoming the first ethnically Iranian monarch to unify Iran in over 850 years. Though they had made him a powerful king, Ismail feared the influence of the Qizilbash over the Iranian people. Ismail and his successors would spend the next 80 years diminishing the threat posed by the foreign Qizilbash, replacing them with slave soldiers from the Caucasus. Nevertheless, the Qizilbash maintained a place of honor within the Safavid Empire, both on the battlefield and at court.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_QIZILBASH_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Poland -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BARBICAN">
			<Text>Barbican</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BARBICAN_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BARBICAN_TEXT">
			<Text>A Barbican is a fortified outpost or archery tower, forming part of a city's outer defense. The towers were often situated with a clear line of fire towards the city's gates, and connected to the city walls via a walled road called the 'neck'. The most famous barbican was built in Kraków in 1499 during the reign of Jan Olbracht. Its construction took inspiration from two other Barbicans in Torun (1429) and Chelm (1449), and was built in response to the danger posed by encroaching Ottoman and Wallachian forces.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Barbicans became obsolete in the 15th century due to improvements in siege tactics and artillery. The Warsaw barbican, erected in 1540, was an anachronism long before it was completed. The tower was used only once by the Swedish in 1656, while trying to prevent Poland from retaking the city. The Swedish had captured the city without a fight two years prior.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BARBICAN_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PANCERNY">
			<Text>Pancerny</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PANCERNY_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PANCERNY_TEXT">
			<Text>Towarzysz Pancerny (Mailed Companion) was a rank of Polish cavalryman from the 10th to 18th century, named for their chainmail armor. Pancerni were organized into companies, with each company consisting of 60 to 200 horsemen. Exceptionally well-armored, they used chainmail or platemail armor, vambraces, helmets, and buckler shields. The most common armaments were sabres, reflex bows and, with the arrival of gunpowder, flintlock pistols and carbines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After the rise of heavy cavalry the Pancerni often worked in concert with the newer and more heavily armed husaria, augmenting a cavalry charge and chasing down routing enemy soldiers. By the second half of the 17th century, they represented approximately 70% of all soldiers in the Polish military, fighting against Cossacks, Tatars, and the Swedish. The Husaria and Pancerni were eventually combined to form the 'Kawaleria Narodowa', the Polish-Lithuanian National Cavalry.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_PANCERNY_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Polynesia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARAE">
			<Text>Marae</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARAE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARAE_TEXT">
			<Text>A Marae (or Malea) is a communal, sacred space in most Polynesian cultures. The Marae usually takes the form of a clearing, sometimes bordered with stones or posts, and sometimes with an accompanying shelter behind it. In most Polynesian cultures, the function of the Marae declined or disappeared with the arrival of Christianity, but it has retained its communal and cultural significance with the Maori of present-day New Zealand.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARAE_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VAKA_NUI">
			<Text>Vaka Nui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VAKA_NUI_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VAKA_NUI_TEXT">
			<Text>The distinctive twin-hulled catamarans developed by the Austronesian people are perhaps the earliest examples of open-ocean vessels. These exceptionally stable craft enabled Polynesians to explore and settle islands across the Pacific Ocean. Catamaran designs have had a resurgence in modern times because of their many advantages over single-hulled ship designs. This revitalization of catamarans has also renewed interest in Polynesian navigation and shipbuilding, with numerous recreations of traditional Polynesian craft being built for both cultural and research purposes.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_VAKA_NUI_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Portugal -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CACADOR">
			<Text>Caçador</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CACADOR_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CACADOR_TEXT">
			<Text>The Caçadores were the elite light infantry of the Portuguese army in the 18th and 19th centuries. The divisions were famed for their marksmanship and their brown coats, one of the first attempts at military camouflage. After Portugal's sound defeat and occupation by Napoleon, the English intervened on behalf of their ally to rally and reorganize a joint war to retake the country. The British general, William Beresford, formed the Caçadores to fill a skirmishing role analogous to the German jaegers or American ranger divisions. Under this combined military, the Caçadores helped in reclaiming Portuguese independence and distinguished themselves as the "fighting cocks" of the Portuguese army until the units were eventually dissolved in the military reforms of 1911.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CACADOR_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA">
			<Text>University of Coimbra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_HELP">
			<Text>Possible Theming Bonuses:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +10 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Foreign[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_WRITING] Great Works of Writing from [COLOR_CYAN]different Eras[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_TEXT">
			<Text>Opened in 1290, the University of Coimbra is one of the oldest centers of higher learning in the world. The university was founded by King Dinis as the Lisbon Estudo Geral, originally with faculties of Arts, Law, Canon Law and Medicine. As the first and only university in Portugal for 350 years, the University of Coimbra became a focus of educational, political, and social influence in Portugal.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_OF_COIMBRA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Rome -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORNIX">
			<Text>Fornix</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORNIX_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORNIX_TEXT">
			<Text>A Roman Triumphal Arch, or Fornix, are freestanding archways designed to span over roadways, a monument you can walk through that is emblematic of Roman architecture. During the Roman Republic, Fornices were constructed in honour of generals who led the Romans to a great victory. The general would lead a parade through the city of Rome until arriving at the senate. Often the festivities were prolonged by a series of games and banquets. Late imperial Romans emulated the semi-mythical tradition of the triumph and its arches, but the archways started to be used more loosely to commemorate the deaths of various emperors, the founding of new colonies, and the construction of other infrastructure. The use of large arches as war memorials has continued to the present day.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORNIX_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VILLA">
			<Text>Villa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VILLA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Roman Improvement. Cannot be built on Resources or adjacent to a City or another Villa.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]A [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource appears on a resourceless tile adjacent to the Villa on construction, claiming the tile if it is unowned. The [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource is removed when the Villa is removed.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the tile, and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Plantations.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Farms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VILLA_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VILLA_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Villae were country homes of upper class roman citizens. Over the progressive conquests and expansion of Roman territories and wealth, the villa evolved from relatively simple getaways for social elites into extravagant centers of sprawling agricultural landholdings called Latifundia, an ancient precursor to today's agribusinesses. The first latifundia were created from land confiscated from conquered peoples in the early 2nd century BC in Magna Graecia (Southern Italy). The Latifundia system expanded with later conquests into Spain and North Africa.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]These estates depended on forced labor for their productivity, often supplied by the enslavement of the same people who occupied the land before conquest. The Latifundia consolidated agricultural production into larger estates with greater economies of scale; owners re-invested profits by purchasing small neighbouring farms to increase their own holdings. Evicted from their farms and replaced by slave labour, the Roman peasantry were forced to find work in the cities of Rome, though often resorting to squatting and handouts.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Latifundia became the template upon which later European nations would base their imperial experiments. The Spanish are especially noteworthy for patterning the Encomienda system after the late Roman Latifundia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_VILLA">
			<Text>Build a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_VILLA]Villa[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_VILLA_HELP">
			<Text>Constructs a Villa, which yields [ICON_CULTURE] Culture on the tile and gives [ICON_FOOD] Food permanently in the [ICON_CAPITOL] Capital.[NEWLINE]On completion, a [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource appearson a random adjacent resourceless tile, claiming the tile if it is unowned.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Plantations Receive +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Adjacent Farms Receive +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_VILLA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and spawn a [ICON_RES_FIGS] Figs Resource.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold to adjacent Farms, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to adjacent Plantations.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Russia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POGOST">
			<Text>Pogost</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POGOST_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POGOST_TEXT">
			<Text>The Pogost as an institution of Russian rural life existed for nearly a millenium, and in that time it underwent multiple transformations. In many medieval Russian states, Pogosts began as inns and lodging for the nobility and priesthood, but may have doubled as community centers and trading hubs. By the end of the 10th century, however, Pogosts had evolved into administrative and legislative hubs throughout the Slavic states. By 1775 the last Pogost-led administrative district was abolished, and the buildings were repurposed as parishes of the Eastern Orthodox Church.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POGOST_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LICORNE">
			<Text>Licorne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LICORNE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LICORNE_TEXT">
			<Text>Licorne is the French name given to the Russian 'unicorn' cannons, named for the distinctively shaped handles on the gun barrels. Devised in 1757, Licornes were a flexible design, easy to fire and transport and made in many differing weights and power. Lighter designs are best remembered from their use as mobile horse artillery, a Russian innovation that would change the European theory of combined arms for the next century.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_LICORNE_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Shoshone -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VP_ENCAMPMENT">
			<Text>Encampment</Text>
			<Gender>neuter:an</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VP_ENCAMPMENT_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VP_ENCAMPMENT_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]A tipi is a conical tent, traditionally made of animal skins, and wooden poles. The tipi was used in the encampments of nomadic tribes of the Great Plains in North America. Tipis are stereotypically associated with Native Americans in the United States in general, however Native Americans from places other than the Great Plains mostly used different types of dwellings. The tipi is durable, provides warmth and comfort in winter, is cool in the heat of summer, and is dry during heavy rains. Tipis could be disassembled and packed away quickly when a tribe decided to move and could be reconstructed quickly upon settling in a new area. This portability was important to Plains Indians with their nomadic lifestyle. Modern tipi covers are usually made of canvas. Contemporary users of tipis include historical reenactors, back-to-the-land devotees, and Native American families attending powwows or encampments who wish to preserve and pass on a part of their heritage and tradition.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_VP_ENCAMPMENT_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built on flat land tiles, and cannot be adjacent to another Encampment.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile. Any enemy unit which ends its turn next to this tile takes 5 damage (damage does not stack with other improvements).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]If within 2 tiles of an Encampment in Shoshone territory, all Shoshone units gain +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_VP_ENCAMPMENT]Encampment[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT_HELP">
			<Text>+15% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile. +20% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength to any nearby Shoshone Units within a 2-tile radius. Any enemy unit which ends its turn next to the Encampment takes 5 damage.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can only be built on flat land tiles, and cannot be adjacent to another Encampment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ENCAMPMENT_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE]Provides a combat bonus for nearby Shoshone units and a defensive bonus for own units on the tile, and lightly damages adjacent enemy units.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BUFFALO_POUND">
			<Text>Buffalo Pound</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BUFFALO_POUND_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BUFFALO_POUND_TEXT">
			<Text>Buffalo Pounds were large constructions built by many Plains Tribes for the entrapment and killing of Buffalo. Large herds of buffalo were corralled and funneled into the pound, a sturdy circular ring of hides and wood, where tribesmen could throw spears and other missile weapons from the safety of the walls.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Buffalo were a staple food source on the North American Plains, but hunting such large animals was difficult without horses or sturdy weapons. With the arrival of Europeans and the introduction of the horse and musket, Native American tribes could travel great distances and attack bison herds with impunity. The good times would not last, however, as Europeans encroached upon this way of life. Increasingly, the Great Plains were converted into farms and pastures for American homesteaders. The American buffalo was driven to the brink of extinction by a combination of habitat loss, industrial-scale hunting, and culls engineered to starve the indigenous population.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Today, American buffalo have recovered, but their range has been greatly limited to a few national parks. Commercial farming and sport hunting continues, but the buffalo are unlikely to ever return to their historical numbers.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BUFFALO_POUND_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YELLOW_BROW">
			<Text>Yellow Brow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YELLOW_BROW_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YELLOW_BROW_TEXT">
			<Text>Yellow Brows (Sh. Ohamupe) were one of two military societies within the Shoshone, playing an integral role in hunting, scouting, and policing within their bands. Yellow Brow braves shaved their heads into a cockscomb 'mohawk', and painted their exposed heads yellow, hence their common English name.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Yellow Brows were composed of only the bravest and most daring of the young men, tasked with keeping order on hunting expeditions, scouting, and soldiering. The Society never had more than a few hundred members at a time; members elected their replacement upon graduation. A young Yellow Brow was expected to act and speak in a contrarian way as a sign of membership.  For instance, when asked if he would like to join the Yellow Brows, it was expected that the young man would say 'No' as a sign of willingness to join, or 'Yes' if he wished to decline.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In battle, Yellow Brows were led by a war chief who carried a long cane tipped with a stone or metal dagger.  The cane was used to grab and unhorse opponents, or as a No-Retreat signal. If the enemy was gaining the upper hand, the chief would drive his staff into the ground and the braves would defend him to the last. Yellow Brows were banned from leaving their chief's side until another member of the tribe came and released the braves from their charge. Deserting the chief was met with abject mockery, and often resulted in banishment from the tribe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_YELLOW_BROW_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Siam -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELEPHANT_CAMP">
			<Text>Elephant Camp</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELEPHANT_CAMP_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELEPHANT_CAMP_TEXT">
			<Text>Often thought of as ceremonial and military implements first, perhaps the greatest contribution of elephants to human society has been as beasts of burden. Elephants are prized as a labour force even in modern times for their ability to haul the dense teak lumber found only in Burma and Thailand. The strength of a fully grown elephant is matched only by its grace, navigating difficult and uneven terrain while carrying heavy loads. With their delicate command of the forest trails, elephants also reduce the potential damage of logging roads to the surrounding forest.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The jobs of Southeast Asia's working elephants have come under threat within the past few decades with the mechanization of logging. Elephants and their mahouts have been forced to look for work in tourism and religious festivals, jobs which elephants find terribly stressful.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELEPHANT_CAMP_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Elephant Camp's main strength comes from adding +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to Lumber Mills. This adds a lot of value to these already strong improvments, so from the start of the game, strongly prioritize settling near Forests and Jungles and avoid chopping them down. Additionally, try to maintain many City-State Allies that have access to Strategic Resources to benefit from the +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold in every Elephant Camp for each. This Building will likely always be a priority to build as the base is already strong, so think about how you can research Technologies to unlock it as soon as possible.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SUEA_MOP">
			<Text>Suea Mop</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SUEA_MOP_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SUEA_MOP_TEXT">
			<Text>Despite Siam's remarkable diplomacy, they did occasionally come into conflict with the western imperial powers which threated their independence. When the French set their sights on Laos, the Siamese mistakenly believed the English would support them against France and prepared for war. The Suea Mop ("Crouching Tiger") were the most technologically advanced cannons in the Siamese arsenal at the time; coastal artillery which could destroy any French boats foolish enough to enter their harbours. However, no amount of raw power can account for corruption and disorganization; the French managed to establish their beachheads, and the coastal artillery of Thailand remained unused. It turns out that the finest artillery money can buy still needs to be fired.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SUEA_MOP_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Suea Mop lacks the Combat Strength bonus when attacking Cities, making it similar to a normal Ranged Unit. However, it deals an extra 15 damage to Units if it hasn't moved before attacking on the turn. This ignores damage reduction and high combat strength of attacked Units, so it effectively makes Suea Mop just as effective when attacking Cities (the extra damage is dealt to all garrisons) and very effective when fighting Units, especially if they are more advanced than you. Furthermore, the Coastal Artillery Promotion is powerful when using Suea Mop as coastal defense, so your Cities with water access are safer than they otherwise would be. As it has low Combat Strength, to avoid moving before attacking you will have to carefully position your army.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]For Promotions, Logistics has the strongest synergy with Suea Mop because you can apply the 15 damage twice per turn, or you can move after attacking which will not affect this bonus next turn. Alternatively, the Range Promotion will allow you to be stationary with more safety giving more reliability in dealing the bonus damage.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Songhai -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMEY">
			<Text>Gumey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMEY_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMEY_TEXT">
			<Text>Gumeys were riverside entrepots used to conduct goods and soldiers back and forth along the Niger river before they were loaded onto camels for the arduous journey across the open desert. Even before gaining their independence from the Mali Empire, the Songhai had become fantastically wealthy off the trade of gold, salt, and slaves from the Trans-Saharan trade routes. The Songhai's seat of power lay at the edge of the vast Saharan desert, acting as a waystation between the Taghazan salt mines to the north, the gold mines in the southwest, and distant markets in Egypt and the Middle East.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMEY_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SOFA">
			<Text>Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SOFA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SOFA_TEXT">
			<Text>Sofa is a Mandinka term for slave soldiers who served in the army of the various Empires of West Africa. Originally, the Sofas were horse grooms of the soldier-nobility, the Farari, but their role slowly changed to become skirmishers and soldiers in their own right. Sofas were recruited from "jonow" (slaves) captured in battle or bought from afar. The institution of slavery in the Mali and Songhai Empires heavily rewarded loyalty, and jonow could rise to civil or military positions of prominence. Jonow became part of their master's clan, and were often freed after a certain amount of years.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sofas were equipped with two quivers, and their bow was small by European standards, so sofas employed deadly poisons and fired in arcs to give their arrows strength.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SOFA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Spain -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SPAIN_INQUISITOR">
			<Text>Inquisition</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_SPAIN_INQUISITOR">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_INQUISITOR}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Nobody expects the Spanish Inquisition![ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Hacienda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_HACIENDA_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_HACIENDA_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Haciendas are colonial estates constructed by the Spanish for the administration and extraction of resources from their native subjects. Haciendas were based on grants of property and enterprise, rather than the strict grant of indigenous labor as described by the older Encomienda system. Haciendas were generally large estates, but the nature of the work varied from plantations, to mining, to factories.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The owner of a Hacienda was called a Hacendado, but the wealthy landowners rarely visited their holdings and preferred to live in nearby cities. Day-to-day operations of a Hacienda were the responsibility of hired managers. Some unusually large and profitable Haciendas were the property of the Roman Catholic Church, exacerbating tension between native laborers and their Christian taskmasters.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Hacienda system was abolished in most countries after the dissolution of the Spanish Empire, but with mixed results. Efforts to break apart the large estates into individual holdings for subsistence farmers led to crushing poverty in some South American nations. In contrast, Latin American and Filipino Haciendas were mostly left intact, but without the same legal standing or permissions of their colonial past.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>Cannot be built adjacent to another Hacienda. Gains additional yields for each adjacent Resource:[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Bonus Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Strategic Resources[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Luxury Resources</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_HACIENDA">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_HACIENDA]Hacienda[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_HACIENDA_HELP">
			<Text>+3 [ICON_Food] Food for each adjacent Bonus Resource, +3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for each adjacent Strategic Resource, and +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for each adjacent Luxury Resource. Cannot be built adjacent to another Hacienda.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_HACIENDA_REC">
			<Text>It will increase [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE]Provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production if adjacent to bonus, strategic and luxury resources respectively.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BULLRING">
			<Text>Bullring</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BULLRING_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BULLRING_TEXT">
			<Text>An exceptionally old and irrepressible institution, Spanish bullfighting can trace its roots back to pre-Roman pagan bull cults. The modern incarnation of Spanish bullfighting traces its roots to the ceremonial and stylistic innovations of virtuoso bullfighters and the construction of the first dedicated Bullrings in the late 1700s. From there, Spain's bullfighting traditions have spread to all of her former colonies.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BULLRING_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Bullring expands on the Zoo's terrain bonus by providing extra [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism on Pastures, Forests, and Jungles. It also add unique bonuses around "We Love the King Day" by generating [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and [ICON_PEACE] Faith when a "We Love the King Day" triggers scaling with Era and a City enters a "We Love the King Day" whenever it completes a Public Works Project.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]To take advantage of the terrain/improvement bonus, you should try to settle and conquer Cities that have lots of Pasture resources, Forests, and Jungles especially after unlocking the Bullring.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The "We Love the King Day" bonuses are the most significant part of the Bullring and once they are constructed, Cities should try to trigger as many "We Love the King Days" as possible. Building Public Works Projects is obviously a unique way for Spain to do this but you should consider prioritizing options that trigger "We Love the King Day" in all Cities like [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Great Merchant Trade Missions especially if you have a large number of Cities with Bullrings.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARMADA">
			<Text>Armada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARMADA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARMADA_TEXT">
			<Text>The "Great and Most Fortunate Navy", the Spanish Armada, was a fleet of 130 ships constructed for the invasion of England and the overthrow the tyrannical Reformist, Elizabeth I. The Armada was one of the largest fleets ever seen in Europe, raised at great expense by Philip II in retribution for England's break from the Catholic Church, their execution of Mary, Queen of Scots, their support for the Dutch revolt against Spain, and the illegitimacy of Elizabeth I.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Spanish ships were outnumbered by England's navy, but they easily outgunned the smaller English vessels. In the end, however, it was not firepower, but speed which won the day, allowing the small English vessels to harry the lumbering Spanish Juggernaut, sinking 10 ships. When finally forced to retire to Spain, a navigational error blew the Armada off-course and onto the Irish coast, where fierce storms dashed the ships against the rocks. When the Armada managed to reach Spain, only 67 of the original 130 ships remained, full of sickly, starving, and demoralized sailors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The lessons of the Spanish Armada informed naval strategy for the next two centuries. Cannons and ranged action had now overtaken boarding and ramming as the primary methods of attack; sinking, rather than capturing, was now the priority. With this stunning victory, England had wrested naval dominance from Spain, a lead they would maintain until the rise of the United States in WWII.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"I sent the Armada against men, not God's winds and waves".[NEWLINE][TAB]- Philip II</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARMADA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Armada's main bonuses are significantly higher [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength if the unit starts its turn at full health and the generation of [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points when it destroys an enemy unit. To take advantage of the first bonus, aim for an overwhelming first strike against the enemy while your fleet is at full health. You'll be significantly weaker after taking damage.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This means that you want to prioritize anything that gives your ships extra [ICON_MOVES] movement and make sure to scout well so that you can outmaneuver your enemy to get a decisive first strike before they can use ranged attacks to damage your ships.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The second bonus encourages using Armadas to land the killing blow. The extra [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admiral Points should allow you to generate [ICON_GREAT_ADMIRAL] Great Admirals more quickly and in greater numbers than usual, which can then be used to provide additional [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength and heal your fleet to keep up the momentum in key moments.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Sweden -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASTU">
			<Text>Bastu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASTU_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASTU_TEXT">
			<Text>The Swedish Bad Stuga (bath cabin), or Bastu, is a small cabin designed as a bathing and dry heat spa. A stove or furnace heats the room to 200°F before patrons enter, where they will recline and sweat. Bastus are a social affair, places for discussion and relaxation with family and friends, but were also places for food curing and childbirth in earlier times.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It is not known where or when Scandinavian sweat baths were first created, but it was well before the Christianization of Scandinavia, as evidenced by their ubiquity throughout medieval Europe. By the time written accounts first described Scandinavian sweat baths, Nordic countries had already created varied and distinct cultures surrounding them.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The health benefits of heat baths are many and varied. Sessions have been shown to relieve cold symptoms and increase pain thresholds. They also help with rheumatic pain and fatigue, and may even reduce the risk of dementia. Prolonged use of a sauna has been linked to reduced male fertility, however, and heat baths should never be enjoyed while under the effects of alcohol.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASTU_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Bastu's main unique bonuses are that it doesn't require Fresh Water, gets extra [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from working Tundra tiles, and generates [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when expending any [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person scaling with Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first two bonuses are primarily focused on where you settle Cities as it allows you to have less priority on settling Fresh Water locations and improves the yields of working Tundra tiles which aligns with Sweden's start bias.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The third bonus is the most impactful as it generates a significant amount of [ICON_CULTURE] Culture that scales with Era and by the number of Cities that you've built a Bastu in. This means you generally want to focus on generating all types of [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People to trigger this as often as you can and this synergizes well with Sweden's Unique Ability and Nobel Committee.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You also want to try to expand aggressively using Sweden's military bonuses and be willing to settle Cities without Fresh Water and in Tundra that other civs might not prioritize so that you can build as many of the Bastu as possible.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOBEL_COMMITTEE">
			<Text>Nobel Committee</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOBEL_COMMITTEE_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOBEL_COMMITTEE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Nobel Prizes are awards administered by the Nobel Foundation and granted in accordance with the principle of "for the greatest benefit to humankind". The prizes were first awarded in 1901, marking the fifth anniversary of Alfred Nobel's death. Each laureate is required to give a public lecture on a subject related to the topic of their prize. The laureates are given a sum of money when they receive their prizes, depending upon how much money the Nobel Foundation can award each year. As of 2023, the monetary award per prize category is 11 million Swedish kronor (SEK), equivalent to approximately US$ 1.035 million. After the award ceremony in Sweden, a banquet is held in the Blue Hall at the Stockholm City Hall, which is attended by the Swedish Royal Family and around 1,300 guests. The Nobel Peace Prize banquet is held in Norway at the Oslo Grand Hotel after the award ceremony. The Nobel Prizes are widely regarded as the most prestigious awards available in their respective fields, and play a major role in the academic calendar and are widely reported on globally.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NOBEL_COMMITTEE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Nobel Committee's main unique bonuses are that it's available two technology tiers earlier, extra [ICON_RESEARCH] Science to each [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Work, extra [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to each Academy, extra [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to each Public School, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold scaling with Era plus [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence to all City-States that you've met when expending a [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]To take advantage of all these bonuses, you primarily want to focus on building Public Schools in every City and focus on generating as many [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People as possible. This synergizes well with Sweden's Unique Ability and the Bastu as they all provide bonuses based on expending [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The bonus [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence to all City-States that you've met can be quite significant if you are generating [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People frequently. This can allow Sweden to Ally many City-States to either shift towards a Diplomatic Victory or open additional fronts against your enemies to push towards a Domination Victory.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Venice -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO">
			<Text>Piazza San Marco</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO_TEXT">
			<Text>Piazza San Marco (often known in English as St Mark's Square), is the principal public square of Venice, Italy, where it is generally known just as "the Piazza" (la Piazza). All other urban spaces in the city (except the Piazzetta and the Piazzale Roma) are called "campi" (fields). The Piazzetta (the 'little Piazza') is an extension of the Piazza towards the lagoon in its south east corner (see plan). The two spaces together form the social, religious and political centre of Venice and are commonly considered together.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Venetian replacement for the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC}. In addition to the bonuses of the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC}, {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO} provides additional [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CITY_SECURITY] City Security, and [ICON_WAR] Military Supply, and an extra boost to the city's [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation. This building also reduces the cooldown of purchasing civilian units and removes the cooldown of purchasing military units. Unlocks the ability for Venice to build 1 of 3 unique buildings once [COLOR_CYAN]Guilds[ENDCOLOR] is researched. Unlike the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC}, the {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO} is made available with the discovery of [COLOR_CYAN]{TXT_KEY_TECH_WRITING_TITLE}[ENDCOLOR], does not require a {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONUMENT_DESC} in the city, but can only be built in the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO_HELP">
			<Text>Unlocks access to [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Murano Glassworks[ENDCOLOR], [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Arsenale di Venezia[ENDCOLOR], and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Rialto District[ENDCOLOR] once [COLOR_CYAN]Guilds[ENDCOLOR] is researched.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIALTO_DISTRICT">
			<Text>Rialto District</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIALTO_DISTRICT_TEXT">
			<Text>The Rialto is and has been for many centuries the financial and commercial centre of Venice. It is an area of the San Polo sestiere of Venice, Italy, also known for its markets and for the Rialto Bridge across the Grand Canal. The area was settled by the ninth century, when a small area in the middle of the Realtine Islands on either side of the Rio Businiacus was known as the Rivoaltus, or "high bank". Eventually the Businiacus became known as the Grand Canal, and the district the Rialto, referring only to the area on the left bank.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIALTO_DISTRICT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of three mutually exclusive buildings that Venice can build in its capital after it has completed {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO}. This building provides an additional [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] trade route slot; boosts the value of [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes to and from the City; generates [ICON_GOLD] Gold based on your empire population; reduces the [ICON_GOLD] Gold cost of purchasing Units and Buildings in the empire, and provides additional [ICON_DIPLOMAT] World Congress Delegates based on your [ICON_GOLD] Gold income.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RIALTO_DISTRICT_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENALE_DI_VENEZIA">
			<Text>Arsenale di Venezia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENALE_DI_VENEZIA_TEXT">
			<Text>The Venetian Arsenal is a complex of former shipyards and armories clustered together in the city of Venice in northern Italy. Owned by the state, the Arsenal was responsible for the bulk of the Venetian republic's naval power during the middle part of the second millennium AD. It was one of the earliest large-scale industrial enterprises in history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENALE_DI_VENEZIA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of three mutually exclusive buildings that Venice can build in its capital after it has completed {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO}. This building boosts [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and Internal [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes; increases [ICON_STRENGTH] City Strength and [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Military Supply from population; and buffs the [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength and [ICON_MOVES] Movement of all naval units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENALE_DI_VENEZIA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURANO_GLASSWORKS">
			<Text>Murano Glassworks</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURANO_GLASSWORKS_TEXT">
			<Text>Murano's reputation as a center for glassmaking was born when the Venetian Republic, fearing fire and the destruction of the city's mostly wooden buildings, ordered glassmakers to move their foundries to Murano in 1291. Murano glass is still associated with Venetian glass. Murano's glassmakers were soon numbered among the island's most prominent citizens. By the fourteenth century, glassmakers were allowed to wear swords, enjoyed immunity from prosecution by the Venetian state and found their daughters married into Venice's most affluent families. While benefiting from certain statutory privileges, glassmakers were forbidden to leave the Republic. However, many of them took the risks associated with migration and established glass furnaces in surrounding cities and farther afield, even in England and the Netherlands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURANO_GLASSWORKS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>One of three mutually exclusive buildings that Venice can build in its capital after it has completed {TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PIAZZA_SAN_MARCO}. Boosts the value of Great Person tile improvements and villages for all cities, enables or strengthens Historic Events on [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Route completion, and contains 2 slots for [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works of Art or Artifacts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MURANO_GLASSWORKS_HELP">
			<Text>Possible Theming Bonuses:[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +8 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GREAT_WORK] Great Works.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_THEMING_BONUS_MURANO_GLASSWORKS">
			<Text>Murano Masterpiece Collection</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MURANO_GLASSWORKS_THEMING_BONUS_HELP">
			<Text>To maximize your bonus, make sure both Great Works were created by the Building Owner.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_CATTARO">
			<Text>Cattaro</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_CORFU">
			<Text>Corfu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_CORON">
			<Text>Coron</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_CANDIA">
			<Text>Candia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_CHIOGGIA">
			<Text>Chioggia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_MODON">
			<Text>Modon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ERACLEA">
			<Text>Eraclea</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_AQUILEA">
			<Text>Aquilea</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SPALATO">
			<Text>Spalato</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ZADAR">
			<Text>Zadar</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FUSTA">
			<Text>Fusta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FUSTA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FUSTA_TEXT">
			<Text>Fusta, or galliots, were small galleys with no more than 35 sailors. Exceptionally light and fast, the Venetians originally used them to maintain a standing navy against pirates, but the ship quickly became a favorite of the pirates themselves. The shallow draft, maneuverability and speed of the Fusta made them a legend throughout the Mediterranean.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_FUSTA_STRATEGY">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_01">
			<Text>la nave Armera</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_02">
			<Text>la nave Bernarda</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_03">
			<Text>la nave Choresa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_04">
			<Text>nave Contarina</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_05">
			<Text>la Contessa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_06">
			<Text>la nave Donada</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_07">
			<Text>la Figa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_08">
			<Text>la Gradeniga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_09">
			<Text>la nave Grimana</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_10">
			<Text>la Liona</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_11">
			<Text>la nave Malipiera</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_12">
			<Text>la Marcella</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_13">
			<Text>la nave Marzella</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_14">
			<Text>la nave Mosta</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_15">
			<Text>la nave Pandora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_16">
			<Text>la nave Panthea</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_17">
			<Text>la nave Pasqualiga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_18">
			<Text>la Permarina</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_19">
			<Text>la Simitecola</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_20">
			<Text>la nave Soranza</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_21">
			<Text>la nave Vendramina</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_22">
			<Text>la nave Veniera</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_23">
			<Text>la nave Zustignana</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_24">
			<Text>la Micella</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_GALLEASS_25">
			<Text>la nave dita la Mema</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Zulu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IZIKO">
			<Text>Iziko</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IZIKO_HELP">
			<Text>Possible Theming Bonuses:
  			[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +4 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Foreign[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_WRITING] Great Works of Writing.
  			[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET] +4 [ICON_CULTURE] and [ICON_TOURISM] for two [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Domestic[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_GW_WRITING] Great Works of Writing.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IZIKO_TEXT">
			<Text>An Iziko is a simple hearth used as a gathering place for Zulu communities. The fireplace was revered as a source for food, warmth, dreams, and ancestral ties. It is from these gatherings that a sense of community and identity was formed, and young Zulus could perform and bond.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The fireplace is used metaphorically for the "cooking of songs" in isicathamiya stage performances, a modern offshoot of traditional Zulu music. Dreams were an essential part of communicating with ancestors and formed part of a deeply rooted Zulu religion. Some isicathamiya musicians claim some of their songs were created in the spiritual realm or given to them by their ancestors.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"A person is a person because of other people"[NEWLINE][TAB]- Zulu proverb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IZIKO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Iziko's main unique bonus is that it provides culture when any of your units level up and scales with the number of cities you have it built in your empire. This synergizes well with the Zulu Unique Ability as less experience is needed for each unit level.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]To maximize the bonus, you should try to build instead of purchase military units so they start with full experience and have as many buildings and other bonuses that provide starting unit experience. You'll also generally want to play aggressively with Zulu so you can be actively gaining experience through combat to level up your existing units and expanding to have more cities to build the Iziko.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA">
			<Text>InDuna</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_HELP">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_TEXT">
			<Text>An InDuna can widely be translated to any leader of men, in commerce, in politics, and in war. An InDuna guided each regiment, or 'ibutho', of young Zulu men and he in turn answered to senior izinDuna who controlled the corps. One or more of these elder chiefs might accompany a big force on an important mission, but there was no single "field marshal" in command of all Zulu forces. Regimental izinDuna, like the non-commissioned officers of today's army, were important for morale and discipline. This was demonstrated during the battle of Isandlwana, where the army led by Ntshingwayo kaMahole outmaneuvered and destroyed a British column. Ntshingwayo kaMahole and his fellow izinDuna snuck a Zulu force of 20,000 men behind the British, hiding them in a valley only 7 miles from the British camp. When discovered sitting in complete silence by scouts, the izinDuna spurred their men into action and closed the remaining distance with lightning speed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The InDuna's primary unique bonuses over a Great General are that when expended it provides experience to the unit it's stacked with and creates an Isibaya which places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource adjacent to it and adjacent Pastures receive [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Isibaya should still primarily be used for military purposes like a Citadel but where possible trying to build it within the working radius of a city and adjacent to Pastures should be considered so you get the economic bonuses.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You should always make sure to have a military unit stacked with the InDuna when constructing an Isibaya and its usually best to try to give the bonus experience to higher level units especially ranged or siege units. This is due to these unit types being easier to keep alive longer compared to melee units and that they tend to gain experience slower so the bonus experience is more impactful.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_01">
			<Text>Mzilikazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_02">
			<Text>Mbopa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_03">
			<Text>Ntshingwayo kaMahole</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_04">
			<Text>Nathaniel Isaacs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_05">
			<Text>Ndlela kaSompisi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_06">
			<Text>Umgobhozi Ovela Entabeni</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_07">
			<Text>Nongalaza KaNondela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_08">
			<Text>Dabulamanzi kaMpande</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_09">
			<Text>Dambuza Nzobo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_10">
			<Text>Nqoboka Mthiyane</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_11">
			<Text>Mabhodla Mbuyazi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_12">
			<Text>Menziwa Biyela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_13">
			<Text>Gala ka Nodade</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_14">
			<Text>Vumindaba kaNthati</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_15">
			<Text>Mavumengwana kaNdlela</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_16">
			<Text>Zibhebhu kaMaphitha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA_17">
			<Text>Manyosi</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ISIBAYA">
			<Text>Isibaya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ISIBAYA_TEXT">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ISIBAYA_HELP}[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An Isibaya is a Zulu homestead and defensive structure. The Isibaya is laid out in a circular pattern with a cattle enclosure at the centre, ringed by huts, palisades, and mud walls. The layout and function are reminiscent of a European corral, hence the Afrikaans term for Amabaya, "Kraal".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cattle were central to the life and economy of the Zulu Kingdom. Cattle were a sign of status, wealth, and power, and were instrumental for feeding and arming the amabutho regiments of the Zulu army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ISIBAYA_HELP">
			<Text>Unique Zulu Great Person Tile Improvement, replacing the Citadel. Can only be constructed by a {TXT_KEY_UNIT_INDUNA}.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Adjacent Pastures receive [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Building an Isibaya claims adjacent tiles and places a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource adjacent to it.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Units standing on an Isibaya receive +100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Tile Defense. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ISIBAYA">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ISIBAYA]Isibaya[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ISIBAYA_HELP">
			<Text>Can only be built in owned territory or adjacent to your own borders in an unowned tile, and cannot be adjacent to other Isibaya. Removes any feature on the tile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Constructing the Isibaya will expand your Cultural borders to surround the Isibaya, increase your [ICON_WAR] Military Unit Supply Cap by 1, place a [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle Resource on an adjacent tile, and will consume this unit. If the new Cultural border claims hexes already owned by another civilization, you will incur a diplomatic penalty as a result.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+100% [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Strength for any Unit stationed in this tile. Deals 30 damage to adjacent Enemy Units. Provides [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture to adjacent Pastures. Contains [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fortifications[ENDCOLOR], allowing owned Units to stay stationed in this tile after attacking and a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Canal[ENDCOLOR], allowing friendly [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Sea[ENDCOLOR] Units to traverse through it.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
