<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2/18/2013 1:17:48 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_01">
			<Text>Jerusalem</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_02">
			<Text>Hebron</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_03">
			<Text>Lachish</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_04">
			<Text>Jericho</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_05">
			<Text>Bethlehem</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_06">
			<Text>Nazareth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_07">
			<Text>Meggido</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_08">
			<Text>Beer-Sheba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_09">
			<Text>Joppa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_10">
			<Text>Hazor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_11">
			<Text>Michmash</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_12">
			<Text>Bethel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_13">
			<Text>Samaria</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_14">
			<Text>Tirzah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_15">
			<Text>Jazer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_16">
			<Text>Shemesh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_17">
			<Text>Shiloh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_18">
			<Text>Kinneret</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_19">
			<Text>Ataroth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_20">
			<Text>Dor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_21">
			<Text>Gezer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_22">
			<Text>Gibeon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_23">
			<Text>Arad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_24">
			<Text>Beth-horon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_25">
			<Text>Geba</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_26">
			<Text>Shikmona</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_27">
			<Text>Emmaus</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_28">
			<Text>Jabesh-Gilead</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_29">
			<Text>Dan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_30">
			<Text>Horem</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ISRAEL_31">
			<Text>Kadesh</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ISRAEL_ADJECTIVE">
			<Text>Israelite</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ISRAEL_DESC">
			<Text>Israelite Empire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ISRAEL_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Israel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_DOM_TEXT">
			<Text>
				May the Lord bless you and Keep you, honorable King David of Israel. As the second king appointed by God's servant Samuel, you succeeded in unifying the Israelite tribes and established its first lasting dynasty. The tales of your conquest of Jerusalem and numerous military campaigns to secure the borders of Israel live on within the Tanakh, now the cornerstone of Western religious and intellectual thought. Under your holy guidance, the Kingdom of Israel grew into a regional power and would see prosperity and security for generations to come.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Though numerous as the stars in the sky and the sand on the seashore, your people turned from their God and against each other, fighting amongst themselves until at last swallowed by the mighty Assyrians and Babylonians. Your once great nation now lies scattered amongst the gentiles, longing for a messiah to unite them. Will you listen to their cries? Will you build a civilization that will stand the test of time?
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_1">
			<Text>History</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_1">
			<Text>The Israelite people have a deep and complex history spanning thousands of years. Much of that history is focused on the land of Canaan and on Israel's conquest, ownership, banishment, and reclamation of that land. Through many generations, and across vast distances, the nation of Israel has retained a strong sense of their cultural and religious heritage, forming ethnoreligious enclaves throughout the western world. Many, including the Israelites' own Jewish descendants, might see Israel as a 'chosen people', set apart from other nations. Despite this view and the distrust that it engenders between groups, the Jewish people have contributed massively to the enrichment of humankind, producing an outsized number of the world's greatest writers, scientists, philosophers, economists, and humanitarians.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_2">
			<Text>Climate and Geography</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_2">
			<Text>Israel is located between the Mediterranean Sea to its west and the Jordan River to its east. The climate varies from mild winters and hot, long summers on the Mediterranean coast, to semi-arid and cooler weather in the mountainous areas, near the border with Syria, to deserts in the Negev region to the south. This wide variety of climactic regions, from semi-tropical to desert, makes Israel exceptionally diverse for its small landmass.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Israel is somewhat tectonically active, with serious earthquakes every few hundred years. The land lies on top of the Dead Sea Transform, which forms a deep rift on Israel's eastern border, forming a series of basins between the tectonic plates, including the Dead Sea, the Sea of Galilee, and the Hula Valley. The Sea of Galilee is the lowest-lying freshwater lake in the world, while the Dead Sea, at -430m below sea level, is the lowest point on earth that isn't underwater.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_3">
			<Text>From Abraham to Moses</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_3">
			<Text>According to the Hebrew Tanakh, Israel's story begins with God -- the one and only -- visiting Abram. God told Abram to move his family to Canaan and that his descendants would possess that land. Abram, now called Abraham, had two sons: Ishmael and Isaac. When Isaac grew up, he also had two sons: Esau and Jacob. When Jacob grew up, he had twelve sons! Each of Jacob's sons would become the patriarch of one of the twelve tribes of Israel (except Levi doesn't count and Joseph got to be two tribes).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Because of a terrible famine in Canaan, Jacobs' entire family moved to Egypt, where their descendants were enslaved by the Egyptians. After a long period of slavery, God revealed himself to a Hebrew prince named Moses, who went back to Egypt to tell the Israelites about God, lead them out of slavery, and take them back to Canaan. Of course, no one has ever found archaeological proof, or Egyptian records saying anything about enslaving the Hebrews, so we have no evidence that any of this actually happened.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_4">
			<Text>The Conquest of Canaan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_4">
			<Text>Where we do have real proof of the Israelites starts with their conquest of most of Canaan by 1000 BCE. From various tribes of pastoralists and outlaws sharing a common Semitic language, a stronger, unified cultural identity began to take root, possibly as a reaction to Egyptian and Philistine meddling in the region after the Bronze Age Collapse. As the Israelites would tell it, however, The Hebrew people conquered the whole of Canaan in a single generation through a series of vicious battles. The books of Joshua, Judges, and Samuel describe a lot of brutal fighting with the Israelites beating all sorts of people, but were in desperate need of a king to guide them. All the cool nations have kings, after all, so I guess Israel better have one too.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_5">
			<Text>Kingdoms of Israel, Judah, and Samaria</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_5">
			<Text>There is not much evidence to suggest a single Israelite state ever existed, but we do have lots of evidence of two Israelite kingdoms: Israel and Judah. Together, the two nations covered very lucrative trade routes between the Mediterranean and the Fertile Crescent, as well as prime olive and wine country. The Israelite kingdoms had a generally favourable relationship with the Phoenician city states to their north, but had tense relationships with the much more powerful Neo-Assyrian Empire. Samaria fell to an Assyrian attack in 722 BCE, and the Assyrians implemented a mass deportation policy, replacing the region with non-Israelites. Judah became a vassal of the Assyrians until their own empire's collapse. The resulting power vacuum in the Levant resulted in the rise of the Neo-Babylonians, who conquered Jerusalem in 586 BCE.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_6">
			<Text>The Jewish Exile and Diaspora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_6">
			<Text>After the fall of Jerusalem, the Babylonians took all the nobility and upper-class Israelites back to Babylon. While in exile there, the Israelites formed a renewed identity as Jews, setting themselves apart from other cultures by their emphasis on ritual purity, symbols, and the observance of holy days like the Sabbath. It was during this exile that most of the Tanakh was written, telling a very different story of where the Israelites came from and how they should think of themselves.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When Babylon fell to the Acheimenid Empire in 539 BCE, Cyrus I decreed that the Jews could return to Jerusalem. This decision was very popular with the Jews and Cyrus got a lot of good press for it, even being called the Jewish Messiah, or savior. Of the Jews that returned to Israel, the generation of exile had already changed them so much that they didn't really have much in common with the Israelites who had stayed in Judah after Jerusalem fell. Many of the Jews decided to stay in Babylon or move to other places throughout the new Persian empire. With each successive empire -- the Persians, the Greeks, and then the Seleucids -- the Jewish people continued to multiply and move throughout the new empires, establishing Jewish communities distinct from local cultures and peoples.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When the Roman consul Pompey conquered the lands of Israel in 64 BCE, they named the region 'Palestine', and set a king as governor over the region. the Jewish people didn't like the Romans at all, and staged three major revolts against Roman occupation. In 137 CE, The Romans decided they'd had enough and barred all Jews from entering Jerusalem.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Blocked off from their traditional place of worship and their historical roots, Jewish thinkers and religious leaders were forced, once again, to change their perspectives in order to retain an identity in a world where they didn't have a homeland. Rabbinical Judaism became far more distinct as a spiritual practice, and less of a political praxis, allowing Jews to assimilate somewhat into their non-Jewish surroundings while preserving their identity as God's chosen people. They never forgot their promised land and the stories preserved in their Tanakh, which would later form the basis for Christian and Muslim holy texts in the centuries to come.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_HEADING_7">
			<Text>Zionism, Mandate Palestine, and the State of Israel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ISRAEL_TEXT_7">
			<Text>The late 19th century saw the rise of a new movement among the far-flung Jewish communities: Zionism, a Jewish nationalist movement to match the rise of the nation-state in Europe. The re-establishment of a Jewish homeland appealed to many Europeans as well, since they liked the idea of Jews living somewhere far away from Europe. The creation of a Jewish nation in Israel also appealed to many Christians, who thought that giving Israel back to the Israelites would bring about the end of the world. After the fall of the Ottoman Empire after World War I, the British controlled Palestine and allowed for larger amounts of Jewish immigration back into Palestine. There was only one problem: There were lots of people already living in Palestine, and they weren't too pleased with so many Jewish refugees coming in.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Arab, Syrian, Lebanese, and the various other communities had a tense relationship with Jewish settlers, mostly Russian refugees from the pogroms. These tensions broke out into civil war when, after the horrors of World War II and the Holocaust, the newly formed United Nations recommended a new Jewish state in Israel. In 1948, Israeli Prime Minister David Ben-Gurion implemented the UN partition plan in 1948; Egypt, Syria, Jordan, and Iraq declared war the following day. Fueled by a rapidly growing population of Holocaust survivors and Jewish nationalists from around the world, the Jewish population in Israel exploded. International public opinion was strongly in favour of the fledgling nation, providing money and arms to defend against another 3 wars fought between Israel and its Arab neighbours. To this day, the issue of occupation and removal of Palestinians remains a point of contention between Israel, the Arab world, and the international community.</Text>
		</Row>		
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_HEADING_1">
			<Text>History</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_TEXT_1">
			<Text>
				David, according to the Hebrew Bible, was the second king of the United Kingdom of Israel. His life is dated to c. 1040–970 BCE, his reign over Judah c. 1010–1002 BCE, and his reign over a United Kingdom of Israel c. 1002–970 BCE.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Books of Samuel, 1 Kings, and 1 Chronicles are the only sources of information on David, although extra-biblical sources do confirm the existence of a Judean royal dynasty called the House of David during the mid-9th century BCE. He is depicted as a righteous, but fallible king, as well as an acclaimed warrior, musician, and poet. David is traditionally credited for composing many of the psalms contained in the Book of Psalms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]David is a central figure in Jewish, Christian, Islamic and Baha'i doctrines and culture. Biblical tradition maintains that a direct descendant of David will be the 'anointed', or messiah. Jewish followers continue to wait for this messiah to lead the Nation of Israel, while Christians maintain that the Messianic prophecies were already fulfilled in Jesus Christ. Islam holds no concept of a Messiah, but still considers David a great prophet and divinely-appointed king.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_LIVED">
			<Text>1040–970 BCE.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_NAME">
			<Text>David, Son of Jesse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_SUBTITLE">
			<Text>King of Israel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_DAVID">
			<Text>David</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADER_DAVID_TITLES_1">
			<Text>The Psalmist</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_CHOSEN_PEOPLE">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat bonus vs. Barbarians and 40 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from clearing Barbarian Camps, scaling with Era. +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from Great Person Improvements and Great Works. [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Cannot build Temples.[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_CHOSEN_PEOPLE_SHORT">
			<Text>Chosen People</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_MACCABEE">
			<Text>Maccabee</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_MACCABEE">
			<Text>Elusive front-line land Unit. Only Israel may build it. Starts with the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Cover I[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Hasmonean Guerilla[ENDCOLOR] Promotions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ANTIQUITY_ISRAEL_MACCABEE_TEXT">
			<Text>The Maccabean revolt began in 167 BCE against Israel's occupiers du jour, the Seleucid Empire in retaliation for the instalation of an altar to Zeus the Greeks' campaign of forced Hellenization against the Jewish people. At the time that there was no organized Jewish army, so Judah the Maccabee organized a protracted guerilla war against the Greeks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After a stunning victory by the Israelites in 166 BCE, the Maccabeean forces ran amok across the countryside, destroying pagan altars, circumcising young boys, and forcing fellow Jews into outlawry. After many battles, the rebels retook Jerusalem and rededicated the Temple. A large punitive force was sent to retake the city, but was forced to return on the death of their emperor, Antiochus IV, affirming religious freedom throughout Judea. The Jewish festival of Hannukah commemorates the rededication of the Temple.  According to Rabbinic tradition, the victorious Maccabees could only find a small jug of oil that had remained uncontaminated by virtue of a seal, and although it only contained enough oil to sustain the Menorah for one day, it miraculously lasted for eight days.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ISRAEL_MACCABEE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Maccabee is a powerful guerilla warrior, most effective in friendly territory. The unit is able to flank and outmaneuver enemy forces, and heal more quickly if inside your territory.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_0">
			<Text>Shammua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_1">
			<Text>Shaphat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_2">
			<Text>Caleb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_3">
			<Text>Igal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_4">
			<Text>Nahbi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_5">
			<Text>Palti</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_6">
			<Text>Gaddiel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_7">
			<Text>Gaddi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_8">
			<Text>Ammiel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_ISRAEL_9">
			<Text>Sethur</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ">
			<Text>Kibbutz</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ_HELP">
			<Text>Only Israel may build it. May only be built on farms and never adjacent to another Kibbutz. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to adjacent Farms and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Great Person Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ_TEXT">
			<Text>A kibbutz is a collective community in Israel that was traditionally based on agriculture. The first kibbutz, Degania, was established in 1909 by predominantly Russian and Eastern European Jewish farmers. Kibbutzim began as an outgrowth of the Bilu movement, a combination of socialism and Zionism set on the agricultural settlement of the Land of Israel in reaction to the Russian Jewish Pogroms.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Today, farming has been partly supplanted by other economies, including industrial plants and high-tech enterprises. In recent decades, some kibbutzim have been privatized and changes have been made in the communal lifestyle. There were 270 kibbutzim in Israel as of 2010; their factories and farms account for 9% of Israel’s industrial, and 40% of its agricultural output, worth over 9.7 billion USD. Some Kibbutzim have developed high-tech and military industries, including military plastics and ammunition.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ">
			<Text>Establish a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_KIBBUTZ]Kibbutz[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ_HELP">
			<Text>Only Israel may build it. May only be built on farms and never adjacent to another Kibbutz. Provides Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. [NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Farms and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to adjacent Great Person Improvements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KIBBUTZ_REC">
			<Text>Establishing a Kibbutz will increase [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture!</Text>
		</Row>

	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>