<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FARM_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every 2 Farms adjacent to this Farm and/or from Fresh Water.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FARM_REC">
			<Text>It will boost your [ICON_FOOD] Food output on this tile. Farms adjacent to two other Farms and/or to Fresh Water gain +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_TRADING_POST_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built over a Road that connects two Cities, doubled if built over a Railroad instead. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if a Trade Route passes over this Village, doubled in post-Industrial era.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_LUMBERMILL_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 2 Lumber Mills adjacent to this Lumber Mill.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CONSUMED_HELP_CUSTOMS_HOUSE">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed. +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built over a Road that connects two Cities, doubled if built over a Railroad instead. +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold if a Trade Route passes over this Village, doubled in post-Industrial era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Great Tile Improvements will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Towns will improve a Great Merchant's Diplomatic Mission Gold Generation and WLTKD Turns by [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]25%[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CONSUMED_HELP_MANUFACTORY">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Great Tile Improvements will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Manufactories will improve a Great Engineer's Hurry Production ability by [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]10%[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CONSUMED_HELP_ACADEMY">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Great Tile Improvements will connect Strategic Resources on this tile to the trade network. Academies will improve a Great Scientist's Discover Technology ability by [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]10%[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_EMBASSY">
			<Text>Embassy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_EMBASSY_TEXT">
			<Text>Embassies can only be built in City-State territory by Great Diplomats.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first player (and only the first!) to construct an Embassy in a City-State's land [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]earns an extra vote in the World Congress[ENDCOLOR]. No player will receive additional votes for Embassies beyond the first one placed in a City-State's territory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An Embassy cannot be pillaged - once built, they can never be removed, and they will always grant their additional World Congress vote to the original builder. If, however, the original builder is conquered, the conqueror will take ownership of their Embassies, and their votes!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_EMBASSY">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_EMBASSY]Embassy[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CONSUMED_HELP_EMBASSY">
			<Text>Unit will be consumed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Grants [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]1 World Congress Vote[ENDCOLOR] when constructed. Gain +1 [ICON_RES_PAPER] Paper.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_JFD_MACHU_PICCHU">
			<Text>Mountain City</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
