<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 5/5/2013 12:20:29 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALLOWS_MAP_TRADING">
			<Text>Allows the sale of world maps to other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALLOWS_TECH_TRADING">
			<Text>Allows technology to be sold to other civilizations.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ALLOWS_VASSALAGE">
			<Text>Allows you to make rival civilizations your vassal state.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ABLTY_MAP_TRADING_STRING">
			<Text>Allows Map Trading</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ABLTY_TECH_TRADING_STRING">
			<Text>Allows Tech Trading</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_ABLTY_VASSALAGE_STRING">
			<Text>Allows Vassalage</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_MAP_TRADING_TOPIC">
			<Text>Map Trading</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_MAP_TRADING_SUMMARY">
			<Text>A civilization's World Map details every island, ocean, Natural Wonder and civilization that a civilization's explorers have discovered and charted. The trade of a civilization's World Map is available upon the discovery of Military Science, and it will reveal every tile that civilization has explored. World Maps do not provide contact with foreign civilizations, but it will chart their location and allow you to meet them! The value of a World Map goes up depending on how much undiscovered land that civilization can reveal to you: Natural Wonders and Resources are worth far more than vast, featureless oceans. World Maps can become expensive, so be sure to explore the world and cash in on the discovery income!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_MAP_TRADING_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_MAP_TRADING_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_MAP_TRADING_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>What is Map Trading?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_TECH_TRADING_TOPIC">
			<Text>Tech Trading</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_TECH_TRADING_SUMMARY">
			<Text>Once you have acquired the Replaceable Parts tech, you may sell your technological discoveries with another civ, as long as you have an Embassy in their capital.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_TECH_TRADING_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_TECH_TRADING_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_DIPLOMACY_TECH_TRADING_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>What is Tech Trading?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_GAME_CONCEPT_SECTION_26">
			<Text>Vassalage</Text>
		</Replace>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OVERVIEW_TOPIC">
			<Text>Vassalage</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OVERVIEW_SUMMARY">
			<Text>A Vassalage Agreement is an agreement between two civilizations, where one civilization swears fealty to another civilization, becoming their vassal. In exchange for protection against other civilizations, the vassal surrenders their political power, including their right to become Leader of the World Congress and United Nations and ability to declare war (they follow their masters into war).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OVERVIEW_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OVERVIEW_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OVERVIEW_ADV_QUEST">
			<Text>What is Vassalage?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OBTAINING_VASSALS_TOPIC">
			<Text>Obtaining Vassals</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OBTAINING_VASSALS_SUMMARY">
			<Text>Vassals may only be obtained after entering the Medieval Era, and after a civilization has agreed to become your vassal. This agreement takes place in the Diplomacy Trade screen. There are two types of Vassalage: voluntary vassalage and capitulation.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Voluntary Vassalage is bought by the master during peacetime. Civilizations that are weak are more likely to surrender themselves as vassals, provided their new master is strong enough and close enough to protect them. Voluntary Vassalage is an agreement of choice only, and the vassal may choose to leave his master's service after a period of only 10 turns.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Capitulation, also known as "forceful vassalage," comes after a civilization has been defeated in war. In exchange for allowing them to live, the vassal agrees to surrender to their captor. Capitulation provides a number of more benefits to the master. The surrendering civilization agrees to forgive most negative diplomatic relations with the master and is forced to remain their vassal until a number of conditions are met. You can view these conditions in the Vassal Overview.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OBTAINING_VASSALS_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OBTAINING_VASSALS_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_OBTAINING_VASSALS_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>How do I obtain vassals?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_ENDING_VASSALS_TOPIC">
			<Text>Ending Vassalage</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_ENDING_VASSALS_SUMMARY">
			<Text>Vassalage may be ended between two civilizations in a variety of ways. The master may choose to declare war on their vassal, immediately ending vassalage between them. The master may choose to liberate their vassal, immediately ending the vassalage agreement (but also providing a very large diplomatic modifier with them)![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The vassal may also request independence from the master (after some conditions are met). The master always has the option of accepting or refusing their request for independence. In both events, the vassalage agreement is immediately ended, but if a master refuses a request for independence, war is immediately declared between the two civilizations.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Liberation of a vassal and requesting independence from a master are options available through the Vassal Overview. Consult this overview for eligibility requirements.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_ENDING_VASSALS_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_ENDING_VASSALS_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_ENDING_VASSALS_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>How do I end vassalage?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_BENEFITS_TOPIC">
			<Text>Benefits of Vassalage</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_BENEFITS_SUMMARY">
			<Text>Vassalage comes with a variety of benefits for the master. The master receives free Open Borders with the vassal, and a free [ICON_DIPLOMAT] Diplomat in the Vassal's [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital, a percentage of the vassal's [ICON_RESEARCH] Science, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_PEACE] Faith. The master's [ICON_RELIGION] Religion and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism to spread faster in their vassal's territory. The vassal contributes a small levy of units on each new era, the vassal is forced to adopt the Master's ideology, and the vassal is not eligible to host the World Congress or United Nations (unless the vassal founded it, in which case they will become the host of the World Congress until a new host is chosen).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_BENEFITS_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_BENEFITS_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_BENEFITS_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>Why should I obtain vassals?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_TAXES_TOPIC">
			<Text>Taxing Vassals</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_TAXES_SUMMARY">
			<Text>Each vassal player in a team can be taxed at individual rates. This tax is applied through the Vassal Overview and is available immediately after the vassalage agreement is made. All taxes are applied at the start of a turn. Taxes are deducted from the vassal's [ICON_GOLD] Gross Gold Per Turn and are divided evenly amongst the civilizations in the master's team (if there are more than one player). Vassal taxes can be set in intervals of 5% starting from 0% and ending in 25%. Taxes may only be set after a set interval (notifications are sent out when vassal taxes are ready, and the Vassal Overview icon will show a number for the number of civilizations who have a pending tax change).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Heavily taxing a civilization will make them more likely to hate you and rebel against you when able to end vassalage.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_TAXES_DESCRIPTION">
			<Text>{TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_TAXES_TOPIC}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CONCEPT_VASSALAGE_VASSAL_TAXES_ADVISOR_QUESTION">
			<Text>Why should I obtain vassals?</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>