<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 10/29/2014 10:02:30 AM -->
<GameData>
  <!-- Skola -->
	<Buildings>
		<Row>
			<Type>BUILDING_SKOLA</Type>
			<BuildingClass>BUILDINGCLASS_PUBLIC_SCHOOL</BuildingClass>
			<Cost>400</Cost>
			<GoldMaintenance>3</GoldMaintenance>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_SCIENTIFIC_THEORY</PrereqTech>
			<FaithCost>200</FaithCost>
			<UnlockedByBelief>true</UnlockedByBelief>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA_HELP</Help>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SKOLA_TEXT</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<ArtDefineTag>ART_DEF_BUILDING_SKOLA</ArtDefineTag>
			<SpecialistType>SPECIALIST_SCIENTIST</SpecialistType>
			<SpecialistCount>2</SpecialistCount>
			<IlliteracyHappinessChange>1</IlliteracyHappinessChange>
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<ConquestProb>66</ConquestProb>
			<HurryCostModifier>0</HurryCostModifier>
			<IconAtlas>COMMUNITY_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>37</PortraitIndex>
		</Row>
	</Buildings>
	<Building_ClassesNeededInCity>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_UNIVERSITY</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Building_ClassesNeededInCity>
	<Building_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_SCIENCE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>100</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_GREAT_PEOPLE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>5</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Building_Flavors>
	<Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
		<Row>
			<CivilizationType>CIVILIZATION_SWEDEN</CivilizationType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_PUBLIC_SCHOOL</BuildingClassType>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
		</Row>
	</Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
	<Building_YieldChangesPerPop>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
			<YieldType>YIELD_SCIENCE</YieldType>
			<Yield>33</Yield>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_SKOLA</BuildingType>
			<YieldType>YIELD_CULTURE</YieldType>
			<Yield>20</Yield>
		</Row>
	</Building_YieldChangesPerPop>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA">
			<Text>Skola</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SKOLA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Swedish state schools are funded by tax money. This goes for both primary and secondary school (Swedish: grundskola), high school (Swedish: gymnasium) and universities. When studying at a university, however, you might have to pay for accommodation and literature. There are private schools as well who also receive funding from the government, but they may charge a fee from the parents.
				Compulsory education starts at seven years of age, with an optional year in förskola (pre-school). The Swedish primary school is split into three parts; Lågstadiet – “the low stage”, which covers grades 1 to 3. This is where you learn the basics of the three main subjects – in Swedish called kärnämnen – Swedish, English and mathematics. It also includes some natural science. Mellanstadiet – “the middle stage”, which covers grades 4 to 6, introduces the children to more detailed subjects. Woodwork and needlework, social and domestic science, and even a second, foreign language in grade 6, a B-språk (B-language). The languages available are usually French, Spanish or German depending on the school. Högstadiet, “the high stage”, is the last stage of the compulsory education, between grades 7 and 9. This is when studies get more in-depth and are taken to an international level.
				Swedish children take national exams at grades 3, 6 and 9. Children at grade 3 take these exams in two of the three main subjects: Swedish and mathematics. In grade 5 the exams extend to the third main subject, English, and in grade 9 the exams also extend to natural science, foreign languages, and one of the four subjects in "Samhällsorientering" (geography, history, religious studies, and civics). They first receive grades in grade 6. The grading system is letter-based, ranging from A-F, where F is the lowest grade and A is the highest. F means "not approved", while all other ratings above F mean "approved". There are only objectives for E, C and A; D means the person has met most (but not all) objectives for C, while B means the person has met most objectives for A. When applying to gymnasium (high schools) or universities, a meritvärde (“meritous point value”) is calculated. E is worth 10 points, D 12.5 points, C 15 points, and so on. Children not being approved in Swedish, English and mathematics will have to study at a special high school program called the “individual program”. Once they are approved, they may apply to an ordinary high school program. Swedes study at high school for three years, between the ages of 16 and 18.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Swedish replacement for the Public School. This building is cheaper and costs less maintenance than the building it replaces, and also boosts the city's [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKOLA_HELP">
			<Text>Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Illiteracy. +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens, and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 3 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the City.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<!-- Basilica -->
	<Buildings>
		<Row>
			<Type>BUILDING_BASILICA</Type>
			<BuildingClass>BUILDINGCLASS_TEMPLE</BuildingClass>
			<FreeStartEra>ERA_RENAISSANCE</FreeStartEra>
			<Cost>150</Cost>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_PHILOSOPHY</PrereqTech>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_DESC</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BASILICA_TEXT</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_HELP</Help>
			<ArtDefineTag>TEMPLE</ArtDefineTag>
			<MinorityHappinessChange>1</MinorityHappinessChange>
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<ConquestProb>66</ConquestProb>
			<HurryCostModifier>25</HurryCostModifier>
			<IconAtlas>COMMUNITY_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>33</PortraitIndex>
		</Row>
	</Buildings>
	<Building_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_RELIGION</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>100</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_GOLD</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Building_Flavors>
	<Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
		<Row>
			<CivilizationType>CIVILIZATION_BYZANTIUM</CivilizationType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_TEMPLE</BuildingClassType>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
		</Row>
	</Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
	<Building_YieldChangesPerPop>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<YieldType>YIELD_FAITH</YieldType>
			<Yield>50</Yield>
		</Row>
	</Building_YieldChangesPerPop>
	<Building_ResourceYieldChanges>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<ResourceType>RESOURCE_INCENSE</ResourceType>
			<YieldType>YIELD_CULTURE</YieldType>
			<Yield>1</Yield>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<ResourceType>RESOURCE_WINE</ResourceType>
			<YieldType>YIELD_CULTURE</YieldType>
			<Yield>1</Yield>
		</Row>
	</Building_ResourceYieldChanges>
	<Building_ClassesNeededInCity>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_BASILICA</BuildingType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_MONUMENT</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Building_ClassesNeededInCity>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_DESC">
			<Text>Basilica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BASILICA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Latin word basilica, has three distinct applications in modern English. The word was originally used to describe an open, Roman, public court building, usually located adjacent to the forum of a Roman town. By extension it was applied to Christian buildings of the same form and continues to be used in an architectural sense to describe those buildings with a central nave and aisles. Later, the term came to refer specifically to a large and important church that has been given special ceremonial rights by the Pope.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Byzantine replacement for the Temple. This building does not require maintenance, and boosts the city's [ICON_PEACE] Faith output based on the number of [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in the city. Use this building to guarantee the establishment of a religion for Byzantium.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BASILICA_HELP">
			<Text>Reduces [ICON_HAPPINESS_3] Religious Unrest. +1 [ICON_PEACE] Culture from [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense and [ICON_RES_WINE] Wine, and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<!-- Great Cothon -->
	<Buildings>
		<Row>
			<Type>BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</Type>
			<BuildingClass>BUILDINGCLASS_NATIONAL_TREASURY</BuildingClass>
			<Cost>125</Cost>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_CURRENCY</PrereqTech>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_HELP</Help>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<ArtDefineTag>ART_DEF_BUILDING_NATIONAL_TREASURY</ArtDefineTag>
			<NumTradeRouteBonus>2</NumTradeRouteBonus>
			<NukeImmune>true</NukeImmune>
			<TradeRouteRecipientBonus>5</TradeRouteRecipientBonus>
			<TradeRouteTargetBonus>3</TradeRouteTargetBonus>
			<NationalPopRequired>25</NationalPopRequired>
			<NumCityCostMod>30</NumCityCostMod>
			<HurryCostModifier>-1</HurryCostModifier>
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<NeverCapture>true</NeverCapture>
			<IconAtlas>COMMUNITY_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>47</PortraitIndex>
		</Row>
	</Buildings>
	<Building_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_GOLD</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>75</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_TRADE_ORIGIN</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>75</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</BuildingType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_I_TRADE_DESTINATION</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>75</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Building_Flavors>
	<Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
		<Row>
			<CivilizationType>CIVILIZATION_CARTHAGE</CivilizationType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_NATIONAL_TREASURY</BuildingClassType>
			<BuildingType>BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON</BuildingType>
		</Row>
	</Civilization_BuildingClassOverrides>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON">
			<Text>Great Cothon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				A cothon is an artificial, protected inner harbor such as that in Carthage during the Punic Wars around 200 BC. The cothon at Carthage was divided into a rectangular merchant harbor followed by an inner protected harbor reserved for military use only. This inner harbor was circular and surrounded by an outer ring of structures divided into a series of docking bays for ship maintenance, along with an island structure at its centre that also housed navy ships. Each individual docking bay featured a raised slipway. Above the raised docking bays was a second level consisting of warehouses where oars and rigging were kept along with supplies such as wood and canvas. On the island structure there existed a raised 'cabin' where the admiral in command could observe the whole harbor along with the surrounding sea. Altogether the inner docking complex could house up to 220 ships. The entire harbor was protected by an outer wall and the main entrance could be closed off with iron chains.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Carthaginian replacement for the East India Company. Must have built a Market in the city, and have a National Population of at least 25. In addition to the normal bonuses provided by the East India Company, the Great Cothon provides additional gold for both recipient and target of trade routes from the city where it is built, provides two additional trade routes. Unlike the East India Company, the Great Cothon is made available in the Classical Era with the discovery of Currency.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GREAT_COTHON_HELP">
			<Text>Must have built a Market in the city, and have a National Population of at least 25. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Trade routes other players make to a city with the Great Cothon will generate an extra 5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the city owner and the trade route owner gains an additional 3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the trade route. Grants two additional [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] Trade Routes.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>